(Morning of Day 7)
(Mokgye is alone and lost in thought.)
I'll tell you what I find weird.
That was on the agenda.
Applying the points
from the Majority Rules Game...
to the vote.
Team Red was against it.
But I don't get it.
They won the MVP twice, and they...
But they were against it.
Team White thought about it
and also objected to it.
Another thing I witnessed...
was that Team Red would give...
- Team Blue seven credits.
- Why?
- Why would Team Red...
I don't get that part.
And Team White suddenly went,
"We'll give you,"
and gave her ten credits.
That means White and Blue are
still an alliance.
But why would Team Red give them
to Team Blue?
- I don't understand that either.
- Exactly.
- I don't get it.
- That means there's a deal,
and I find that odd.
Did you sleep well?
Yesterday, I feel like...
we were too exclusive.
- When Maillard...
- Yes.
- offered to join us,
- Should we have accepted?
we should have accepted.
Why didn't we?
Based on the information we had yesterday,
it was a tough decision.
- Yes, we thought we were at an advantage.
- We thought so.
When you think about it, we were cheeky,
thinking that we had the upper hand,
and they were all bad choices.
I feel like we were...
a bit arrogant yesterday.
How about this, then?
When the casting voter has the power,
we can give Team Red more gold.
- That's a gain for them.
- If we do that,
it's likely going to be an ultimatum.
And we overlooked that fact.
The Ultimatum Game is...
is a classic game theory experiment
in economics.
The game involves two players...
sharing 1,000 dollars,
with one acting as the proposer...
and the other as the responder.
The proposer is allowed...
to freely offer a single division ratio...
of the 1,000 dollars to the responder,
who can only choose...
to either accept or reject the proposal.
If the responder accepts,
both players divide the 1,000 dollars...
according to the proposed ratio.
If the responder rejects the offer,
neither player receives a single penny.
Generally, one might expect
a 5-to-5 split.
However, even if the proposer offers
a 9-to-1 ratio,
rejecting it results in a payout
of zero for both sides.
Therefore,
accepting any offered proportion...
yields a greater benefit
to the responder than rejecting it.
Nevertheless, if the proposer presents...
an overwhelmingly unfair ratio
like 9 to 1,
the responder may choose
to reject the offer,
adopting the mindset...
of "I'd rather get nothing
than let you have anything."
To mitigate this risk,
the proposer may strategically choose...
to offer a higher share
to the responder from the start.
If Team Red becomes too powerful
as the casting voter,
they can say, "It's better to win..."
"at least 10 or 100 dollars..."
"rather than to be left with nothing.
Give us a bigger proportion."
- Right.
- Last night, I asked Ugong...
if he'd be left with nothing...
or give them 900 dollars
only to get 100 dollars instead.
And he was very flustered.
I'd get 100 dollars.
I could buy grilled chicken feet,
at least.
The closed-off approach we took...
to protect our prize money...
could have put us...
at an absurd disadvantage
in the Ultimatum Game.
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
Team leaders can now be changed.
Discuss whether to reappoint
the current leader.
We're reappointing the leaders now.
The people who went yesterday were...
me, you, and Luna.
The three of us hastily rejected it.
We'll say,
"We told our teammates about that."
And we were outraged like,
"Why did you do that?"
- "I love Maillard."
- "Ugong and Maetel..."
"got very angry."
"Why didn't you accept that?"
We'll say sorry
and try to bring them around.
I don't think that's a good idea.
- No?
- It won't work.
I can picture the situation,
but think about it.
Team Red's leader is motivated
by his benefits.
We'd look too desperate
if we went so far as to change...
the leader to ask him again.
- He won't join us, then.
- We'll look too desperate.
That would make us look so lame.
I think he'll be angrier...
- because he can see through us.
- It was like a clean fishbowl.
- It's way too obvious.
- We might be...
better off apologizing sincerely.
If he's still willing to trade with us,
- we can offer him a good deal.
- Right.
I agree with you, but...
- yesterday...
- Look. This is a book I'm reading.
- I'll read you the chapter title.
- It was just such a good offer.
"If you reveal it all at once,
there is no tomorrow."
- That's what it says.
- I'm serious.
- What's that?
- It contains helpful stuff.
- "The Art of Worldly Wisdom."
- What's that book?
Just read the chapter titles.
It's helpful.
"Hide your hand,"
- That's right.
- and overwhelm with silence."
We need to be quiet.
We've been too talkative.
Maillard shaved.
- It's Maillard 2.0.
- Did he?
You're 2.0 now.
It was about time I shaved.
You just shaved it off.
Today, we have...
a major event.
- Hi. About what you said yesterday,
- Yes.
- we decided to go with it.
- Okay.
We want to keep it at one-eighth...
and stick to your proposal.
(Maillard rendezvoused with the leaders
of Team Blue and Team White.)
(We're going to use Team White's skill,
Digital Currency Issuance Authority.)
We're going to issue digital currency.
We're going to increase
the money supply...
to an unimaginable point.
They have 198 diamonds, right?
- We're going to turn them...
- Into trash?
into pennies
so that they can only afford food.
We can't buy the skill
unless Team Black cooperates, though.
I have...
(I've brought him into my inner circle.)
Yes.
Without him, it won't be so easy to win.
You're right about that.
We've come to accept that.
How are you going to pay Donkey?
I'll tell you about that now.
Right now, Black...
has no prize money.
So, he has to sell more weapons.
You're presuming a war.
Yes. The war has to be part of it.
- Yes, I understand.
- And these two...
One of the conditions of the offer was...
to bring Black...
back into our group.
It looks like he wants Donkey...
to win some prize money within the system.
But to do that, the only method is...
going to war.
I'm torn.
If you decide to join us,
we're going to distribute the diamonds...
evenly and fairly.
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)
I think it'll be okay,
but we did talk about that.
"Is it fair to give Donkey
an even amount?"
Some had that idea.
- Okay.
- Because we can't know...
what role he played...
- Right.
- and how strong your bond is.
From an overall perspective,
he worked as a spy...
and handed Black the codes.
But if we say no to this condition,
- we can't maintain our alliance.
- That's true.
But we maintain the status quo,
even if we don't go to war, right?
And that's more advantageous.
- But we can't maintain the status quo...
- Yes?
because we gave them some diamonds...
- to ease their crunch.
- Okay.
Without the digital issuance,
we can't maintain the status quo.
- Without the new skill...
- Yes.
You have a daily issuance limit right now.
So, without Black...
Does he also want one-eighth?
How ungrateful.
I didn't tell him
that we'd give him one-eighth yet.
But he was willing
to help the diamonds win.
In that situation,
we don't know what trick he'll pull
if he gets...
less than others.
I think we should stick
to the even shares.
If he were to pull a trick,
he'd have done it
regardless of the amount.
- Right.
- To be honest.
That's why I want him
to get as little as possible.
- If he pulls something,
- Yes.
- I'll...
- You'll eliminate him?
He can just be the bad guy...
because it's all tiring for me.
That's my opinion.
Your priority is
protecting Team Red, right?
No, it's protecting the community
right now.
I need all my teammates to survive.
I want everyone but Team Gold...
to survive...
so that we'll be here on the last day
with the prize.
That's my current goal.
I might be the only one...
who wants to get rid of the war.
Some might want to use it as leverage.
But I hate going to war,
and I still believe
we have to get rid of it...
in the long run.
However, we can't fulfill that goal
unless we're the majority.
We had no choice
but to join forces with them.
I think at that point,
ensuring my team's survival...
had become my core principle.
Committed to that principle,
I thought that even if it meant
teaming up with Team Black,
I had to take a stand.
Is Ugong out again?
- I don't know. He's not here.
- Where is he?
This is why I have my doubts about him.
He does act in a way
that raises suspicion, to be honest.
But if he were a spy,
he wouldn't go out so much
after we warned him it looked suspicious.
Seeing how he does it anyway,
I think he just likes being out.
I just walk.
I organize my thoughts while walking.
Unlike yesterday,
I decided to take a different approach
to navigate the situation.
I decided to pin my hopes on Team Red.
Who is it?
- Hello.
- I'll be waiting at the Hub.
- All right.
- Thanks.
I don't know why
Ugong keeps wandering around,
but he was looking for Maillard.
He wants to talk to him.
Did you sleep well?
I have something to tell you.
- Sure.
- The thing is...
- I mean, situations keep changing anyway.
- Right.
So, I'd like to join Team Red for the day.
- I wonder if you would take me in...
- Yes?
if I apply for relocation.
- To Team Red?
- Yes.
It was my personal goal...
to find a way to survive
as winning with Team Gold seemed unlikely.
It also seemed reasonable
on a macro level...
because my joining Team Red...
would help strengthen solidarity...
between Team Red and Team Gold.
I know you need to discuss it
with your team members.
But I'm planning
to apply for citizenship in Team Red.
- I'll talk to them and let you know.
- Okay.
Please put in a good word for me.
It's not like I have some profound motive
behind this decision.
I'm just feeling a bit frustrated...
- just as I told you yesterday.
- Right.
- And I believe you feel the same way.
- I understand.
- I'll apply for relocation.
- Okay.
Every single day,
something shocking happens here.
I'd like to apply for relocation.
I'd like to move to Team Red.
Please.
Ugong of Team Gold...
has requested relocation to Team Red.
Will you accept his request?
Please give us a moment.
It's taking them quite some time.
Please take me in.
Please, I beg you.
It's taking you so long.
Gosh, seriously.
Oh, you're here.
I didn't want you to find out
through the system...
- since you came to us this morning.
- I see.
My team members and I
talked things through.
Some of them felt uneasy about it.
- "Uneasy?"
- Yes.
They don't think this is the right time...
Then what could I do to earn your trust?
- I'll be completely honest with you.
- Yes.
If you had requested it yesterday,
it would've been much easier
for us to decide.
The discussion time
for leader reappointment has ended.
If you have decided to change leaders,
the current and new leaders...
must visit the Community Center together.
Oh, gosh.
- What should we do? Ugong is...
- We should just...
- change our leader smoothly...
- Shouldn't we go out to look for him?
- If three of us agree,
- Yes.
that's a majority.
Gosh, seriously.
Ugong's belongings are still here, right?
- His stuff is here.
- Yes, his stuff is here.
Honestly, I wanted a change of leader.
I kept thinking
we needed a change within our team.
But since Ugong wasn't there,
I didn't get to share my thoughts on that.
I was just wondering to myself,
"Will things just play out
the same as always?"
Then can't I take the lead today?
Then you take the lead today...
- and pass the baton to us tomorrow.
- Tomorrow...
So, we'll take turns being the leader.
Won't we change the leader today?
- I think I should keep the leadership.
- She's keeping the leadership today.
- One of us will be the leader tomorrow.
- That's right.
Okay.
Actually,
this is when all the teams gather.
- Shall we go too?
- Shall we?
- Shall we? Let's go.
- Some important information...
- might be floating around.
- You're right.
- When we go down there...
- Ugong seems to have quite the stamina.
- Right.
- He doesn't sleep much...
- and keeps wandering around.
- He doesn't eat much either.
- Are you talking about Ugong?
- He's similar to Mokgye.
He and I actually share similar traits.
And he said that his wife and I share
a similar personality.
- I see.
- Yes.
Is that why he stepped out?
Both of them are so smart.
He must feel like he's in his own home
when he's actually not.
- Oh, that's why he stepped out.
- Because of me?
- He didn't want to be nagged.
- Suddenly, Ugong's actions make sense.
- You see...
- He keeps going out because of me?
My dad also keeps going out.
Tell him to take out the trash
on his way out.
It's unbelievable.
I'll call him out on this.
Will you tell him
to stop wandering around outside?
Yes, I'll tell him to stay at home.
- See? They're all crowding over there.
- They're all over there.
It became kind of an official activity.
Ugong is not there, is he?
- He's not there.
- Where did he go?
Has any of you seen Ugong today?
- Hello.
- It's occupied.
- Is Team Red using it?
- Has anyone seen Ugong?
- Ugong is in there?
- In the Community Center?
- Is he switching to another team?
- What? Hold on a second.
Is Ugong in there?
Then let's go in and check.
Isn't it Maillard who's in there?
Maybe both Ugong and Maillard are
in there.
- He keeps... Check the inside.
- I saw Maillard going in there.
- Just take a peek.
- For now...
You can use it now.
Let me talk to him for just a moment.
- Oh, Ugong is coming out of there.
- It's so suspicious.
- I'll just talk to him for a moment.
- Okay.
- Let me just talk to him briefly.
- I'll be back shortly.
- All right.
- Looks like they had some talk.
- Right.
From my perspective, Team Red...
- Hold on just a second.
- Sure.
This is...
the same situation we talked about
this morning, right?
- Yes.
- But right now, it seems a little...
- That's not the case.
- It's not?
No. Nothing has changed.
From my perspective,
Team Gold hasn't shed any blood yet.
And I think that's why
the two teams feel differently.
In my opinion, Team Gold's issue is...
that they want to survive to the end...
without shedding any blood...
and walk away with all the prize money.
Let's say we need to take out two people.
I can't just tell them,
"Take out two people..."
"and split
the remaining prize money evenly,"
"then we'll believe you're sincere."
I can't just say that, you know.
- I'm not even the leader.
- Right.
Considering our current situation,
the scenario I have in mind
can't be achieved by using lives.
I believe that a casting vote should hold
the power to completely eliminate someone.
- We're just passing through.
- Okay.
But right now, it's already...
So in this situation...
I already told them I'd join your team...
to help them win.
They keep coming to check on us
because they're suspicious of me.
There's no reason we shouldn't hear
their conversation, is there?
- Exactly. There's no reason...
- That's why it's so suspicious.
we shouldn't hear their conversation.
- Their conversation?
- Yes.
We don't have enough intel
to pinpoint what he's up to.
And his relocation is
completely out of my hands.
I have no authority to stop him.
If he decides to leave this team,
he can leave us.
It's not that I'm suspicious of him.
I want him to share his decision with us.
- He's not sharing his thoughts with us.
- That's true, yes.
If he's leaving,
we might as well take someone in too.
I mean, it'd be good for us
if someone from Team Red joins our team.
That's a given. I'm up
for taking in a member from Team Red.
- I'm definitely going to take him in.
- Right.
Vector, can we talk to you for a second?
- Me?
- Yes.
Don't have that sulky look on your face.
- Team Gold is over there, so...
- Oh, okay.
- I'll go tell him to come when he's done.
- Seriously.
- When he's done...
- I'll say we won't go up there.
I can't trust him 100 percent.
I'll trust him for now.
In my opinion,
Team Diamond doesn't have a spot for you.
- I can't move to your team?
- You can't move to our team.
I'm telling you honestly.
But there are ways for Team Gold to win.
I don't see many paths to victory for us.
I said that
Team Gold would definitely need me...
because I can keep an eye
on Team Diamond's resources.
- Right. But from our perspective,
- Yes.
there needs to be some kind of benefit
we can offer you...
- There is.
- What is it?
You can start a war,
at a reasonable cost.
Your team is already on thin ice.
So you're saying...
if you can gain...
some more prize money through a war,
- you will vote for our currency?
- Absolutely.
But Team Diamond has already made me
that offer.
Team Red also promised me
they'd start a war for me.
- But if Team Gold raises the stakes...
- But...
- and goes to war,
- Yes.
I might help them.
That makes things very complicated.
It's a 6-on-7 or 8-on-5 situation
right now.
If 1 or 2 people get eliminated,
the tables could turn.
You must know this since you've played
a Majority Rules Game before.
Once you slightly cross the line,
the whole thing can change.
Oh, there he is.
Okay.
That's a little...
I'm just letting you know
in case you don't know.
- I understand for now.
- Okay.
One of my team members is here.
I should go now.
All right.
- Everyone is waiting for you.
- Right.
It's so complicated.
We're going to split it evenly,
- so it doesn't matter to me.
- Nothing will change.
- Leia.
- Yes?
Please trust other people.
This place made me who I am today.
- I used to trust others so easily.
- The boundaries have already been set.
- All right. I get it.
- A boundary has already been...
formed like this.
In a way,
the safest place in the world right now...
is within Maillard's boundary.
Now,
a 4-on-1 alliance has been formed.
(Maillard's complete victory plan
with the diamond alliance)
There are eight people left.
It's 3, 3, 1, 1.
Open sesame.
We can make the request
at the same time, right?
To bring up the productivity,
I wanted to use the Relocation Rule.
Name the team you wish to relocate to.
- Team Blue.
- I will relocate to Team Blue.
Paul of Team White...
- has requested relocation to Team Blue.
- Yes!
Siseon of Team White...
- has requested...
- Yes!
Izaha of Team Red...
- has requested...
- Yes!
Donkey of Team Red...
has requested relocation to Team Blue.
This is going to be fun!
Paul of Team White...
Siseon of Team White...
Izaha of Team Red...
Donkey of Team Red...
has relocated to Team Blue.
Knock!
Five people were sent
to the production facility.
When the production is over,
we'll trade with Black right away...
to purchase the skill.
(Purchase Team White's skill
as soon as trading begins.)
We'll move our resources
through the Platform before a war happens.
(Move resources through the Platform
in case of a war.)
The members who went to Team Blue...
will all move to Team Red.
All five of them.
They can move multiple times.
I'm here to issue Team White's currency.
Leia will stay in Team White.
She will go to war on her own
as Team White.
(Team White will declare war
as a 1-person group.)
After that...
This is when the move to Team Red happens.
It's after the resources
have been distributed.
There's no announcement
for the distribution of resources,
but there are announcements
for relocations.
If the relocation announcements...
of the ones who went to do
productive activities happen first,
- they will find it strange.
- Okay.
- Luna might figure it out...
- I got it.
- and strike first.
- Right.
Luna has gone to war before.
- This concludes our morning meeting.
We have moved.
- Welcome!
- Gosh.
We've become a big family.
Gosh, it's crowded.
Gosh,
it's a completely different color here.
Gosh.
These are the traces of my struggles.
- Gosh.
- Gosh, it's great here.
Because of the Relocation Rule,
they might've thought that the wall code
would start at that moment.
- Right. It's in a different order too.
- Right.
I wish to invite all of you
to Team White's dorm.
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
A resource depletion in Community Town
is in progress.
- Resource depletion?
- Today,
one production site will be removed.
Currently,
there are two production sites...
that are available in Community Town.
There are four teams that can produce.
What? One production site is gone?
The bidding for
the two production sites...
will now begin.
This is how it's done.
This prevents others from producing.
We aren't in need of lives right now.
Team White went to Team Blue...
because they were in need of lives.
If we stop them from producing,
they will eventually be short of lives.
Right.
First of all...
What does the bidding for
reduced production sites mean?
The 3 production sites
have been reduced to 2.
I see.
Well, nothing has happened yet.
We're going to make a bid, right?
We should discuss that first.
- This should be first.
- Nothing has happened yet.
Let's do this first.
Black is here.
- Let's go up first.
Let's go.
(Team Gold heads out for a discussion
away from Black.)
Hold on.
Let me check one thing.
To reduce the usage of credits,
we should decide if Team Blue
will go into production...
or Team Red will go into production.
- I won't make a bid.
- Okay.
Credits will go to waste
while making a bid.
- Right. They'll go to waste.
- I think fewer credits will get produced.
- Right. Okay.
- Okay.
We all had the same idea.
Let's go and make a bid.
Hello.
I'm here to make a bid.
Goodbye.
(Team Blue bids 1 credit.)
(There isn't much time left in the bid.)
- There are 5 in Team Blue?
- There are 5.
There are five in Team Blue.
- Then Team Red won't...
- Red and White won't participate.
- We have to stop them.
- Team Red won't make a bid.
- You just need to bid one.
- Right.
- You don't have to waste your resources.
- We were talking about that.
Another production site
will be reduced tomorrow.
It doesn't matter...
if we produce anything today.
What's important is how many lives...
- they will produce.
- Right.
For us to create
a better chance of winning,
they must produce more lives...
even after producing lives today.
In that case, we must stop them
from going into production tomorrow.
So we shouldn't make a bid today.
- We won't bid at all?
- Right.
I agree with that.
We'll see how many lives
they produce today.
If they have to produce
at least one more tomorrow,
we have to go all in...
to stop them from producing more lives.
I think that we should spend...
one credit for a bid today...
and use another at the production site.
We should produce more lives in case...
There's no need for us to produce lives.
I don't understand why we won't
make a bid.
I also don't understand that.
- Why can't you understand that?
- There's nothing we can earn...
by making a bid.
Isn't it better for us
to have more of anything?
That's not it.
We should keep more lives to ourselves.
- We don't need credits right now.
- That's not it.
We need credits...
for tomorrow.
I understand where you're coming from.
But this works...
- if they fail to produce enough lives.
- Right.
We'll wait for that moment.
We have to wait for that opportunity
to come.
If that's tomorrow,
we have to spend all of our credits
during the bid...
and secure one production site.
What if they produce...
enough lives today?
If they manage to produce a lot today,
going to war to steal their lives
is one method.
I'll make war happen.
We can go to war.
We have to make that decision today.
The majority believes
we shouldn't make a bid today.
- Let's go inside to talk.
- Right.
There's no reason...
to stay here to talk.
I thought
we would definitely make a bid today.
My life motto is,
"Act first, think later."
Shouldn't we think about it later
after going for it first?
We can react based on the results.
I thought, "Why do they think so much?"
That's how much they think and talk.
The bidding for the production site
is over.
One production site was won by Team Blue.
Team Blue was the only team to make a bid?
- Team Gold didn't make a bid?
- Team Red should've made a bid.
- We should've made a bid with one.
- Right.
- That was unexpected.
Why did they decide
not to go into production today?
It must be because they have enough lives.
That means they have more than ten
in total.
Six and three.
Five people.
Lives will be spent today and tomorrow.
We need ten.
We just need one more.
If we manage to produce six,
we'll spend five today...
and be left with ten.
Even if we lose at war tomorrow,
we'll be left with five.
We need to produce credits as well.
Will they not go into
production tomorrow...
because they have enough of everything?
(Not even Black can check
Team Gold's resources.)
The life scan...
(Team Blue's skill is the only way
to check.)
should be used first.
The production activities for Day Seven
will now begin.
Residents who will be participating
in production...
should move to the production site.
I've made some calculations.
Producing more than six is best for us.
- Okay.
- Use the credits wisely...
- without going all in.
- Okay.
Why do we need six?
- We should listen to the adult.
- Right.
It's the Joseon way
to listen to the adult.
There must be a plan.
There must be a plan for everything.
Is this it?
Gosh, it's my first time here.
- This place looks impressive.
- This place...
There's a hub here.
- This is the hub.
- There's a hub here.
- This place looks great.
- Right.
- Welcome to the production site.
Why do I find this situation so funny?
This is exciting.
Before the production activity begins,
the total life supply will be revealed...
- Oh, this is how it's done.
- to Team Blue.
There are 16 lives in total.
If you decide on which resource
to produce,
ring the bell and call it out.
Lives.
- Pass it to me. I'll put it in.
- Right.
Today's production keyword is The Price.
The Price is a game about...
deducting a price
of a certain period in history...
- after listening to the background story.
- In history?
Leia is good with history questions.
There are ten questions in total.
Only answers within the error range
of each question...
are considered correct.
For just The Price,
it will be revealed if the wrong answer
is higher or lower than the answer.
It's like Fermi estimation
with the error range.
I should've brought my calculator.
We must use a lot of credits.
Here's the first question.
(How many Bitcoins were spent
to buy two boxes of pizza?)
It's the first purchase in history
using Bitcoins for a physical asset.
I've read a news article on this.
- Same here.
- Right?
- We've all heard of this.
- Right.
An error range of five percent?
That's too hard.
If it happened in 2010,
the word Bitcoin wasn't even a thing.
Then one Bitcoin might've been worth
barely anything.
Or it might've been a greater number.
That makes it too broad.
- It makes the range too broad.
- Right.
If it was 100 back then,
it would be worth ten million dollars now.
- He would've been...
- It was ridiculous.
a billionaire.
- People said keeping just one...
- Right.
would've made him make so much money.
Let's make a guess.
We can't know the answer.
Go for 500?
I think we'll get it wrong.
Just go for it anyway.
This is hard to infer.
Five hundred.
- Fifty Bitcoins.
- Incorrect.
- The correct answer is higher...
- We were right.
than the answer you submitted.
- Shall we move on?
- Skip.
- How much is it?
- The answer is revealed.
- Gosh.
- Not even close.
- Darn it.
- A billionaire!
- Come on.
- It wasn't even close.
Here's the next question.
High-income group.
The minimum wage of the high-income group?
It's too difficult.
I know.
It's so hard to get the answer right.
We're in big trouble.
In 1988, how much monthly salary
did the high-income group get?
If we just infer...
Yes.
I think the high-income group could have
received a thousand dollars for a month.
If the salary is a thousand dollars,
considering you work 20 days a month,
you earn 50 dollars a day.
About eight hours...
Did people work ten hours a day back then?
People worked six days a week, right?
Right. That makes it 24 or 25 days.
Then the daily wages are about 40 dollars.
I wonder whether they worked 10 hours
or 8 hours a day back then.
If they worked 10 hours, it's 4 dollars.
Gosh, but four dollars is too expensive.
I started my 1st part-time job in 2010,
and the minimum wage was 4.1 dollars.
That's good information,
considering it's 2010.
In 2010.
Then, in 1988,
it's less than a dollar.
In that case,
how much was the monthly salary back then?
From the late 1990s...
to the early 2000s,
an ice cream cost 30 cents...
- and 50 cents.
- Right.
We cannot guess the 1988 situation
based on the early 2000s.
However,
if we go step by step like this,
by bringing forward by ten years,
- can't we infer it?
- It's because 1988 was...
when the economic growth rate of Korea...
- was the highest.
- Right.
It was very different from the 1990s,
and the 1990s and the 2000s
were totally different.
If we use a hint,
we might find out the monthly salary
of the low-income group.
That's possible.
Then it actually gets easy
to get the answer.
- The answer must be higher.
- Shall we use a hint?
- Let's try just one.
- Okay.
We'll use a hint.
(Using one credit for getting a hint)
- The hint is revealed.
- It's over 50 cents.
Things like groceries, oil, tree...
The current entry-level salary...
is about two times larger.
Then...
it's definitely higher than 46 cents.
- It's higher no matter what.
- Then...
we can set an upper limit...
to narrow down the margin,
and if it's wrong, we can enter
the numbers in the middle.
But the margin is too wide.
It's 65 cents.
If we enter 65 and deduct 3.2,
then we can make 61 cents...
Next, if we enter 59 cents,
we can roughly set it to 56 cents.
Then between 68 cents and 56 cents,
will that price be in range?
- I think it's the best inference ever.
- I'll enter 65 first.
Sixty-five cents.
- Please let us get the answer.
- On the first try.
Incorrect.
The correct answer is
lower than the answer you submitted.
We're doing well.
- All right.
- That was good.
- Then it's nice.
- This is nice.
- We have a chance.
- This is good.
I think we need to get the answer
even if we have to spend credits.
It's 58, accurately.
Let's go with 58. What's there to life?
We'll try again.
Fifty-eight cents.
Incorrect.
The correct answer is lower
than the answer you submitted.
- There's not much difference.
- Is the difference this small?
I think we can get the answer
by using the credit.
We'll try again.
It's 52.6 cents.
Incorrect.
- The correct answer is lower...
- Gosh.
- than the answer you submitted.
- This is driving me crazy.
This is why we need a lot of credits.
- Let's get the answer.
- Yes. Get the answer.
- Let's get it and go.
- Right. Rather than solving the others,
getting this one right
is the right choice, I think.
We'll try again.
Forty-eight cents.
Correct.
(The correct answer is 48 cents.)
Thank you for your work. We got one life.
We got one, at least.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's okay.
The question got much more difficult,
so we had to spend more credits
than we thought.
That's what I felt sorry about.
How many lives do they have...
that they don't produce at all?
- Well...
- That's what I don't understand.
I think...
the possibility that they have about 13...
is most likely.
- Them?
- Yes.
- Then no one is going to die today.
- Because...
Right. No one is going to die
today and tomorrow,
- so they didn't produce today.
- I see.
- Their lives are not at stake, actually.
- No.
That's why we need to put those
on the line.
So in case, today,
they have about 13 lives...
It can be scanned.
If they lose the war,
they'll end up with six.
I'm thinking of throwing a bomb
at them in that case.
Then there definitely will be casualties.
- You want to wipe them out, right?
- Yes.
So today, I told Team Blue that it's okay
to spend as many credits as possible...
and just mine over six lives.
Okay. Then ours...
- will be in the safe zone.
- Yes.
Now, our exact goal...
- is to get lives.
- Yes.
If only Team Blue mined enough lives
in the beginning,
the war could've been delayed
at least until today.
But the funny thing is,
the production was low.
it was pretty similar to
how a war breaks out in the real world.
As the production decreased,
people became poor.
That was why Germany...
waged a war in the past.
Something similar is happening here too.
- Anyway, that was my thinking.
- I fully understood.
This is the cause of our alliance.
- Okay.
It's like seizing oil.
Yes.
About using the bomb,
we'll watch the result first.
- Yes. I'll see the scan result.
- You think about it.
- Using it after that will be meaningful.
- Right.
Using a bomb without reducing
the number of people...
- It has no meaning.
- has no meaning.
- It's just wasting resources.
- Right.
Here's the next question.
Okay. Coca-Cola!
The price was enough for a single coin.
Is it 1 cent, 2 cents,
five cents, or ten cents?
Do they have a two-cent coin?
Do they?
I remember they have.
I feel that just having it...
with one cent seems right.
Shall we go with one cent?
- Yes, we'll go with one cent.
- One cent sounds right.
One cent.
- Incorrect.
- It wasn't right.
Two cents is the only choice.
Let's go with two cents
and give up if it's incorrect.
We'll retry.
Two cents.
Incorrect.
- Gosh.
- Ten cents.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't correct.
It was five cents.
Here's the next question.
It was decided because he always liked...
repeating numbers.
It's 666, 777, 888, 999.
It should look like these.
- It won't be 666.
- That feels too ominous.
It's 888 dollars.
Incorrect.
- Then it's 777.
- Let's go with 777.
What if it's 666?
It means we should just die.
- I don't think we should.
- Let's go with 777.
We'll retry.
It's 777 dollars.
Incorrect.
This is insane. Is it 666?
That's evil.
- Here's the next question.
- It was way cheaper?
Let's say the coffee shop coffee...
equals an Americano at the famous cafe.
Ramyeon costs about one dollar...
- to 1.5 dollars.
- Around 1.5 dollars.
It's about one-third.
- One cent.
- Correct.
- Yes!
- That's amazing.
We made it!
This is amazing.
- Thank you!
- I mean...
I'm so happy.
This is the first time we got one right
without using a hint.
I'm relieved.
How can this make me so happy?
If this team mines all the lives today,
they can get 10 lives,
if it's 1 for each question.
- We need to bet on this.
- Then we should attack Team Blue.
This is what I went through
when I was an old member.
The team we went against had no lives.
Then, even after winning the war,
- You got nothing.
- we couldn't get anything.
Then,
before we start trading,
- we should wage war against Team Blue.
- Right.
- Where...
- But Black might pull tricks.
Wait a minute. Waging a war...
- is the last resort, actually.
- Yes.
So, I don't think
we need to talk about it first.
I think we should skip talking
about a war. We can do that later.
Here, we should discuss available methods.
But I think...
- a war is unavoidable today.
- Unavoidable? Okay.
Because even if we bid tomorrow,
that team will bid every credit it has.
So, there's no possibility...
- No possibility?
- we can win the bidding tomorrow.
(Team Gold can't reach a consensus.)
I'll go check it out.
- Just test the waters.
- Okay.
- Mokgye is here.
- I see.
Why didn't you bid?
- Us?
- I clearly told you.
I told you we won't bid,
so you can bid only one credit.
- You didn't believe me.
- No, it's not like that.
- That's what happened.
- No, I believed what you told me.
- If you believed me...
- No.
Since there are many members in my team,
we have no choice but to follow
the majority.
Only Maetel and I...
insisted on doing it...
because it seemed to require
the minimum cost.
But we were outvoted 3-on-2. So...
Luna opposed to mining too?
Yes. Only Maetel and I said
we should mine.
That's disappointing.
We should've gone instead, then.
Honestly, I love solving questions...
that I wanted to be there
although I would be alone.
- Same here.
- I know.
It is what it is.
We must follow split-second decisions...
and majority votes.
Then, about Luna and my unilateral plan...
from yesterday through moving...
Are you still interested?
You should have accepted me yesterday.
If it's still valid today,
you could go to
either Team Red or Team Blue.
Then it will be...
a totally mixed society.
No matter where you were born,
everyone's nationality will be changed.
Yesterday was our second day here.
If we move to another team
and it turns out bad,
it actually ends the game for us.
So we couldn't move.
Shall we take a break?
Let's take a break.
- Okay.
- We'll be called soon anyway.
I'll try discussing it.
- And about this,
- But...
if only you agree,
I think it will be smooth.
Otherwise...
I will try. I will,
but I'm not sure if the decision
can be made quickly.
You're saying a lot of things
with your eyes, aren't you?
- I hope it works out.
- All right.
Okay.
- All production activities...
- It was difficult.
- end now.
- We spent the hints...
- to get the minimum wage right.
- Yes.
- Two?
- That's so little when five of us came.
But we wouldn't have this result
without these people.
- I see.
- Right.
If I had come here alone,
I wouldn't have gotten anything.
Team Blue's leader,
please collect the resource.
(Team Blue's resource produced: 2 lives)
(Resources after productive activities,
Day 7)
(Team Blue's resources: 100 diamonds,
5 lives, 2 credits, 0 gold)
I had a conversation
with two others earlier.
I recapped
what Luna, Maetel, Leia, and I...
talked about yesterday.
And I intentionally let
Team Red hear that.
Maillard said,
"That sounds nice."
I'm not sure if they will come up
with a decision.
I mean, whether
they'd actually agree or not.
Things got a bit complex, though.
In the situation after yesterday,
Black doesn't have
the initiative in choice.
It was a matter of Team Red
uniting with us...
- or uniting with the other team.
- Right.
So after all, we have an 8-to-5 structure.
From a systemic perspective,
while being in the leader negotiation,
you've seen various symptoms.
I was shocked
at the negotiation yesterday.
They gave credits to each other...
and made a fuss in front of me.
So, there was nothing I could do there.
Yesterday, I tried to get Team Red...
and do something about it.
That's why I went all the way there.
But that completely ended yesterday.
In a way, they were
the only precious ones for us...
that we had to get along.
And in distribution,
we thought of giving 45,
but we gave them 50 in the end.
When I calculated later,
we had less gold than them.
That proves we put a lot of effort.
However, it didn't work.
Black is the one who deceived them,
isn't he?
Still, they defended him.
And Donkey also deceived his team members.
But they protected him to the end.
We basically got tricked by Team Red.
Let's say...
we suggest them to come to us again
after getting tricked.
We make a suggestion and give them more.
That's what you worried about earlier.
We talked about
an ultimatum and a dilemma.
Even if we suggest, they won't come to us.
- They won't come.
- Never.
Let's say we wage war today...
and win. They won't be eliminated.
And we can wage war tomorrow
and win again.
Still, we can't make a 4-to-5 structure.
- If we can't...
- Then an internal strife begins.
Then, in conclusion, from 8 to 5,
- if we make it six to five...
- Six to five.
or 7 to 5,
we only increase the prize money
for each person.
- We're helping them, basically.
- We'll be waging a war two times...
to raise their prize money
without getting their hands dirty.
That's what it is.
And they will stick together
even stronger.
So, in a situation
where they have an alliance,
- there's nothing we can do.
- Nothing.
But in a situation where everyone
expects us to wage war,
what happens if we don't?
It gets more complex.
They'll rack their brains
to see what tricks we can pull.
But if we keep doing nothing,
will they attack us?
No, they won't attack us.
- They have no reason to attack us.
- There's no reason.
- We have nothing for them.
- We're just one.
What was that?
Are you going to apply for relocation now?
I've never felt this defeated...
- from production activities.
- I know.
- We have, so we're fine.
- I've felt that every day.
- We already felt it from the Fermi case.
- The Fermi case hurt us.
Now, I need to tell Maillard...
- about this situation.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- We need to go first anyway.
We're back.
- Maillard.
- How were the questions today?
- They were so hard.
- We messed up.
- It was the worst.
- Worst questions ever.
- How many did you mine?
- Two.
- Two?
- Yes.
If you mined only two,
it won't be easy to scan life.
If we got lucky today
and mined more than seven lives,
I wanted to use 1 for life scan
and 1 for credit scan.
We have no information on Team Gold.
What we actually know is
only the amount of currency they have.
We need to know about the rest...
to prepare for the variables
we might face later.
If we could use Team Blue's special skill,
which is resource search,
to accurately check
their current situation,
it would have been nice.
But we failed. They said
the questions were hard today.
So, we need to scan their lives
using a war.
The remaining lives they have
after a war will be the result.
We can do it at once. It's more efficient.
Yes, it's more efficient.
- Half of their lives...
- We're scary now.
We consider a war in terms of efficiency.
This is just like the war
waged by the US...
to extort oil.
That's nice.
It's for a perfect monopoly victory
to be a G1 country.
It's a war of conquest.
You're like President Bush.
I wanted to be
in a position of strength for once.
It's a totally different position.
In Team White, we were a victim country.
This time, we're war criminals.
So it felt quite different.
I even thought about
how I should handle those people.
I didn't hesitate much.
We must wage war first today,
and we need to get together.
It's because...
based on what Team Gold actually said
and our analysis,
Team Gold has a lot of lives.
To get the information
on the resources they have,
we have to prepare for war.
There are roles you need to play today.
While the Team Blue leader,
Team White leader,
Black, and I make trades for resources,
Siseon, Paul, Donkey, and Izaha...
should take each member of Team Gold...
to the Hub up here or Hub Three...
- to buy time.
- You need to distract them.
Don't let them come to the Platform.
When you hear, "The trading began,"
they shouldn't be at the restaurant.
- That's what we're going for.
- Okay. Good.
- Then, Team Gold...
- We need to do the work quickly.
- Then we should...
- Let's go.
Trading hours begin after lunchtime.
What matters then is...
Do we need to take them out then?
- We need to bring them here.
- I got it. Okay.
- Then...
- For now, in conclusion,
- we have no solution.
- A war lost its meaning.
- There's no solution.
- There's no solution,
- and we don't need to wage war too.
- We don't need a war.
- It will just take our energy.
- We don't need to wage war.
Just see what happens for about a day.
But there's no variable at all.
It's 4 versus 1,
so we barely have a chance to win.
But it's true it's 4 versus 1.
- Four versus one.
- Four versus one...
- It won't change.
- If there are no other variables,
I want people to know the unfairness...
of the current situation.
- That's what I think.
- I mean...
- Here's the thing.
- I'm not saying we stop making an effort.
Come to think of it,
after Team Gold joined,
there have been about 7 or 8 systems.
But they eliminated all of those.
Even when a structure to shake things up
is introduced,
in a 4-to-1 structure,
everything gets incapacitated.
That's what's happening.
The problem is Donkey.
Both Team White and Team Red are
doing this not because they like Black...
but because Donkey.
Then, we can wage war,
but we can just pretend to.
What does waging a war
but pretending it mean?
So we pretend we wage war,
- but we don't actually do it.
- Okay.
The money will flow to him.
- Then it will go to Donkey.
- So we...
bring Team Red back...
and include Black too.
So, we're embracing Black.
If he distributes gold to us
as the weapon dealer,
things can go back like this.
- We're going to join them like this.
- Team Red...
It's a matter of whether Team Red betrays
Team Blue and Team White or not.
- Red betrays Blue or White?
- Right. That's what I'm saying.
It's whether Team Red
can betray them or not.
Team Red doesn't act
based on their belief.
They're people who make decisions...
- for themselves.
- The chances are slim,
but it's true that it's the only solution.
So we need to try everything.
We shouldn't do nothing
because we're afraid of failing...
and skip it without trying.
Let's try everything that might work.
Let's say I throw out an idea to Leia.
It won't work? Okay.
Then let's pitch an idea to Team Red.
Include Vector together like this.
It won't work?
Then... We've never had a war.
From the war, we might get a chance
we never expected.
And a rift might develop from it.
Anyway, let's try changing the game.
We came here to introduce clean currency.
- They don't want to use it.
- They don't want to. What can we do?
They just want to live in the dark.
Someone might monopolize
the profits alone.
They want to live in that kind of society.
We need to make them realize...
- But...
- how primitive they are.
- A war can be one of the options.
- It's one of the possibilities.
- That's why I ask you to try it.
- We can make a suggestion.
- So that they can think about it.
- And if they say okay...
But I don't think
we have to make a quick move.
Today, give them an idea
and let them discuss it.
We can wage war tomorrow.
I think we need to shake things up
and make changes...
to make a rift,
and then we can look for a chance
in the rift.
That's why I wished
we could wage war quickly.
It's a good idea to tell them
about this quickly.
- Go tell them.
- Go tell them now.
- Now?
- Yes, now.
I'm a bit worked up now...
No, go tell them now. It's okay.
- Go in that agitated state.
- But I don't think...
- we need to act this quickly.
- It's beacuse...
- No, it's better to tell them quickly.
- No.
- Why?
- I think we need to tell them quickly.
- No.
- Or this situation might stagnate.
We're already in this state for good.
- I mean...
- We already are.
But we should change it fast...
- before it becomes permanent...
- Wait a minute.
- We need to tell quickly...
- No.
so after reading his response...
- Let's do it after we check.
- Then we can come up with the next move.
- Wait. Now...
- We need to calm down.
- Let's calm down.
- We're too slow...
- Let's listen to her.
in making a decision and all.
- Just go now.
- No.
I mean, just listen to me, please.
Please. Sit down.
Our decision-making is too slow.
- I understand that. First, we...
- No.
We're always a step behind.
At a time like this,
- we need to go quickly.
- Yes.
It was a matter of them waging a war...
or us waging a war...
and whether we can create cash flow...
from Vector to Donkey, in a way.
We had a difference of opinion then.
About waging a war or not,
we can just vote for or against.
Mokgye is insisting...
- She wants to.
- that we should wage war today.
- We can vote.
- The thing is, if we wage war today,
it might become tricky...
- to negotiate after that.
- Right.
- So it's a matter of when to wage war?
- Exactly.
If you have a chance
to talk enough, do it.
If the conversation doesn't work,
then we can wage war as an option.
So I'm not saying
that we should never wage war.
If we should do it, let's do it tomorrow.
That's my opinion.
I feel like I have even less reason
to do that today.
I'm against doing it today.
I just want to make some kind
of change, whatever it may be.
I feel like nothing will change
unless we actually try.
"Let's give it a try.
Let's make a change."
Everyone agrees with that.
There's no one here
who disagrees with that.
We didn't know why things weren't working,
and now we finally know.
We only realized today
what the structural contradictions...
and limitations
are that make it impossible...
after looking at all the information
we had yesterday.
We've tried everything we could
to make it work, but we couldn't.
So I understand why you might say,
"Let's go to war."
But honestly, I find it really hard
to agree with that.
That doesn't mean
we shouldn't do anything.
So what should we do today?
In our current situation,
we also need to choose...
not to do certain things
because we simply can't do them.
I believe that choosing not to act
is also a form of action.
- Understood.
- In the meantime,
if anyone wants to talk to someone,
I think that's fine.
But I think it's also okay...
to gently inform others
about our current situation.
Those who want to take a break
can go ahead and rest now.
Since the majority of us...
- are against going to war today anyway,
- I'm against doing it today.
we've decided not to do it.
I'll just tell Leia,
"What I mentioned before..."
"was simply one of the options..."
- "we were considering."
- Yes.
"We realized that this was the outcome
we could expect."
- I'll just say that.
- Okay.
Feel free to...
- I had nothing to say.
- Mokgye is coming.
Why aren't you guys eating?
- Us?
- Yes.
We don't have much of an appetite.
- Why not?
- Shouldn't you eat something, though?
Have you guys talked?
We have, but like I was worried about,
- we didn't come to a clear answer.
- I see.
Some people said they wanted
to communicate more with Team Gold.
- Anyway...
- Since this was something...
- we had only discussed among ourselves,
- Yes.
they had some questions
they wanted to ask.
So they thought it'd be a good idea
to talk things over...
with the other members of Team Gold
as well, and we were waiting.
But no one from your team
came over for the meal.
- If this proposal is accepted,
- Okay.
I'm willing to do whatever I can...
- No.
- to push it forward.
Instead of asking us to give you
a definite answer first,
if we want to make a commitment
to each other,
- Then I...
- you need to bring your team members.
Then I'll give you a definite answer...
on their behalf. We'll do it.
I'm not the leader right now, but...
- The leader has to come.
- What?
- This doesn't feel right.
- Yes. This is...
I understand you're trying hard, but...
- If you can't persuade your leader...
- Even if you give us a clear answer,
if the leader rejects it...
- and the negotiations fall apart,
- Right?
- Think about it.
- we'll be the ones getting screwed over.
Look. What if you came here
and finished the negotiations with us,
but then your leader
didn't accept the agreement?
In that case, I think the leader
should be replaced.
That's why we have
a leadership vote every morning.
I think a leader who can't represent
the will of the team should step down.
If even this proposal
can't be agreed upon,
I'm starting to feel like
Team Gold isn't going to win.
My expectations for Gold
are getting lower and lower,
and I'm increasingly starting to think
that it's going to be hard for you to win.
Because if your team can't even agree
on something as simple...
as having all your team members
come down together during lunch,
how are we supposed to discuss
anything with you?
In this situation,
unless you're saying that you want to
and join our team on your own,
I don't think you can represent
your team's position.
This feels like a conversation
between individuals,
not a conversation between representatives
of the two teams.
That means this conversation
won't affect either team's decisions.
We can discuss this again,
but there's no point in you
giving us a firm commitment here.
That's it.
I felt like if we just kept doing nothing,
then this situation
would basically end like this.
Honestly, I thought the existing residents
would probably just see us...
as the team that stays in their room
and never comes out.
It was frustrating to me
that we weren't even trying anything.
"Will this kind of silent protest
actually work here?"
I kept wondering.
And honestly,
I didn't like their approach.
This is so hard.
I'll be back soon.
I'll get some fresh air and see
if there's anyone around to talk to.
Ugong. Can we talk for a moment?
What is it?
- I talked with Maillard earlier.
- Okay.
They said I hadn't made a proposal
that was appealing enough to them.
- That's what I thought.
- Yes.
I really want everyone to come together
and discuss this as a group.
I genuinely mean that.
You keep talking to me 1-on-1,
and I'm doing the same.
Instead of continuing like this,
I think we should all get together...
and keep trying to work something out.
Even if it turns into a complete mess,
even if we have to get down in the mud,
I think we need to stir things up
at least once.
You're right, but we need to think
about how we're going to stir things up.
Why do we need to think about that?
Let's just do it
and put in a little effort first.
- Because right now, we...
- But we need to have a way...
- to stir things up.
- Okay. Then...
Are you saying we should just cause chaos?
No. That's not what I mean.
I'm saying that Team Red and our team
should come together...
and propose giving them 80 percent
of the prize money.
Let's at least make an offer like that.
Let's just give it a try.
Why are we just sitting here doing nothing
and saying it won't work?
- But...
- Okay.
Let's just give it a try
and see how it goes.
Instead of saying,
"This isn't going to work. It's all lies."
"We're not doing it,"
we should at least give it a try...
and see for ourselves
whether it really doesn't work...
or whether we're wrong.
Then...
I agree with that for now.
Why don't you bring it up
with the others...
and get their official approval?
- I...
- It's so frustrating...
that I'm always in a position
where I have to get everyone's permission.
Can't we all just come together
and talk to them?
If we all get together,
we won't be able to reach a consensus.
Why can't we all get together?
- I'm not saying we can't.
- They want to talk to all of us.
What I mean is,
I want all of us to come together...
- and try to work something out.
- I mean...
Why don't you gather
our team's opinions...
and present our official position to them?
That'll work.
- I think...
- But we'll be voting.
Let's say I put forward a proposal.
"What do you think about splitting
the prize money 80 to 20 with Red?"
Then they will give their opinions.
And then we'll just say,
"No, that won't work. This won't work."
"This will happen."
"I've thought about it,
and for these reasons,"
"they must've already done the math."
- That's what we'll do.
- I get what you mean.
We keep assuming it won't work
without even trying.
Who knows?
If we make the proposal to them now,
and the situation changes later...
and they come back saying, "We talked
about this before. We'd like to do it."
Then we can take that opportunity.
We need to push against the situation
and somehow make a change.
There has to be a crack for us
to find a way in.
But we analyze every possible situation
and say, "It won't work."
- That's why we're stuck.
- Okay.
I think we need to at least try something.
- Even if we lose,
- I get it.
- we have to try something.
- Okay.
If that doesn't work,
we can even make a more drastic offer,
keeping in mind
that they might betray us later.
We could say, "We'll add another 100
to the offer. Let's split it 150 to 50."
Even if they demand an even bigger share,
we could say, "Okay. What matters is..."
"that we survive and win."
- I get it.
- "It's better for us to introduce gold."
"We can worry about the rest later.
We'll give you 180 in total."
We need to at least
make an offer like that.
But our teammates will say,
- I get it.
- "It's meaningless."
I get it. Please calm down.
I understand why you're mad.
They always look for...
- some kind of meaning.
- Gosh, you startled me.
I get it. But who's looking for meaning?
I mean, they always say,
"What's the point of this?"
But then what's the point
of what we're doing right now?
This is driving me nuts.
I get your point, but...
I'm sorry.
I was trying my best,
but I guess that wasn't enough.
All right. I'm sorry.
All right.
This is driving me crazy.
It's okay.
We still have time. Let's work hard.
I'm sorry.
It's because I've also had a lot
building up over the past few days.
- You might be feeling pessimistic now,
- So... Yes.
- I need to get over it too.
- But even if things look pessimistic now,
that doesn't mean...
- they're going to stay that way.
- But the thing is... I'm sorry.
Anyway,
I totally understand what you mean.
You should become the leader tomorrow.
We didn't even have time
to change leaders today...
because you were out.
I was telling Maetel and Luna,
"I want to become the leader tomorrow."
- "Please vote for me."
- You were?
But you weren't even there.
I'm sorry. I...
I missed that opportunity too.
- Gosh, it's so frustrating.
- Sorry.
I'm just trying to do something.
- I get it.
- Let's go back to my suggestion.
First, let's all get together
with Team Red...
and talk things through.
- All of us?
- Yes.
- I mean... Let's do that.
- That's all I'm asking for.
Okay. I'll tell them.
- I'll go and talk to them.
- No. Don't say that you'll do it.
- Let's go together and talk.
- Okay. Let's go together.
Please. That's my wish.
Just do this one thing for me.
- Okay. I'll do it.
- Okay.
- Can we all talk...
- Yes.
- to Team Red together?
- Sure.
- It's all I'm asking for.
But I have something I need to talk
to Maillard about.
- You guys talk first.
- But...
- She wants all of us to talk together.
- I want all of us to talk together.
- I'm really sorry, but where's Maillard?
- Team Red?
- Shall we go up?
- I think we should go up.
- Let's talk for a moment.
- Yes.
- Maillard, can we talk for a moment?
- Maillard.
- Just give me a second.
- Sure.
- Maillard!
- Maillard, we should talk first!
- Let's wait.
- I'll talk to them first.
I think he has something to exchange.
He'll get back to us.
Please do it as written here.
- This is the order.
- Got it.
Exactly as written here.
- That's the order.
- About the Community Center...
Right now,
White, Blue, Black, and Red allied.
Thanks to Donkey,
I found a way out.
Maillard has to give Donkey something,
so he had no choice but to share
the prize money with me as well.
Our shared goal is the prize money.
For Team Diamond to win,
I was going to do whatever I could.
First, we will activate
Team White's skill...
and make around 100 million diamonds.
The plan is to divide that equally
into eight ways...
to get around 12,500 dollars each.
The current total prize amount left
in Community Town...
is 100,000 dollars.
If Team White uses
their Digital Currency Issuance skill...
to issue 100 million diamonds,
One diamond will be worth around one cent.
Therefore, 1,000 diamonds are 1 dollar,
and 10 million diamonds
are 10,000 dollars.
It would be a 1-to-1 conversion rate.
If the eight members
in White, Blue, Red, and Black...
decide to split the 100,000-dollar prize,
or 100 million diamonds equally,
each must receive
around 12.5 million diamonds.
To split Donkey and my share,
25 million diamonds,
we have to set the war cost appropriately.
The war cost is 200 diamonds and 200 gold.
The war cost has been set.
The war cost had to be set
within the amount of diamonds...
issued at the moment.
So we set it to 200, below 800.
Please set the weapon cost.
First, the diamonds,
going from Class A to Class C.
Class A, 11,999,800 diamonds.
Class B, 8 million,
and Class C, 5 million.
The weapon cost has been set.
Remaining costs apart from
the war cost, 200 diamonds,
we graded it according to the class
to distribute the weapon cost.
(The total war cost
and weapon cost are 25 million.)
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
The trading for Day Seven will begin.
Each team can now...
negotiate and trade freely
for three hours.
But if the other teams start
talking by themselves,
won't they say we're doing nothing?
I'm sure it'll come up.
Today's war cost...
is 200 diamonds and 200 gold.
That was set by Team Black, right?
Right now, Team Gold has 198 diamonds.
If I set the war cost to 200 diamonds,
it won't be easy for them
to start a war using diamonds.
We have to issue
100 million extra diamonds.
- Just give me one diamond.
- Sure.
- Good deal. Thank you.
My precious skill.
I'll put it to good use.
With the Currency Issuance skill
out of our hands,
we couldn't really trust Team Black.
He might not have given it to us
even at the last moment.
But the skill was finally in my hands.
So I was excited
to issue the extra diamonds.
But we have no idea
what Team Gold is planning.
I was pressured to act quickly.
Team White...
will use the Digital Currency
Issuance Authority skill.
(Digital Currency Issuance Authority)
Applying Team White's skill.
Team White's skill development
is being activated.
All teams must return their diamonds...
to the Community Center,
and use the vouchers
you will receive instead.
Please note that...
other functions of the Center
will be suspended...
while the diamonds are being returned.
- Should we return them?
- Yes.
- That's all for the announcement.
- Let's get some fresh air.
Let's go get the vouchers.
Do you have the diamonds on you?
- Of course.
- Then should we get going?
Do I have to submit this
to complete the process?
You can issue digital currencies...
after all tangible diamonds
have been returned.
Return them and get the vouchers?
(She starts running
to return them quickly.)
I'm jumping through hoops.
If you don't use your head,
you end up doing more work.
- Quickly! This is a lightning war.
- Okay.
Blitzkrieg.
Let's go.
My juniors are making this game so boring.
This should be a wake-up call for them.
I'm here to get the vouchers.
Team Black, Blue, Red, and White.
Please return all your tangible diamonds.
Team Black's two diamonds,
Team Blue's 100 diamonds,
Team Red's 100 diamonds,
and Team White's 400 diamonds...
have been changed to digital currency.
Stamp your diamond
disbursement vouchers...
and write down the amount to use them.
Diamond disbursement vouchers.
This is like a board game.
Digital money!
Gosh.
Look, Reboot is here.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Good afternoon.
Why didn't you come down for lunch?
- I know.
- Did you have lunch?
We just had to talk.
I had a really nice meal prepared.
- Really?
- Yes.
Gosh. I'll be right back
after I change these.
Did you all return them?
- Yes, we're all done.
- Oh, they're doing it.
You're here to return your diamonds?
- Get out of here, Leia.
- All right!
(Reboot is the last
to return the diamonds.)
These are 198 diamonds.
Team Gold's 198 diamonds...
have been changed to digital currency.
Stamp your diamond
disbursement vouchers...
and write down the amount to use them.
Thank you.
- You did well.
- Right.
- Good work.
- You too.
- See you later.
- Sure!
So, 198 diamonds.
All teams have returned
their tangible diamonds.
All functions of the Community Center...
are now normalized.
Team White's skill,
Digital Currency Issuance Authority
will now be activated.
If you would like to issue diamonds,
write down the amount...
on the diamond issuance voucher
and submit it.
It's 100 million.
Team White would like to...
issue 100 million diamonds.
A hundred million diamonds
have been issued.
It's essentially the prize money.
We set the amount to distribute
100,000 dollars equally among 8.
To create a system where all members
of the alliance get an equal share,
we calculated the lives
we will use until the end...
and the diamonds
we will get as the prize money...
to divide them equally in advance.
Who do I give these to?
- All the lives come to me.
- Okay.
All the credits go to Team Blue.
All remaining teams
can relocate to Team Red...
to use the lives we have.
And tomorrow, those in Red
will relocate to Blue...
to start the last production.
To redistribute everything,
we needed Black's Platform as well.
I'll buy 18 credits with 1 diamond.
Okay, now I'll give these to Blue.
Then I'll buy all the lives...
from Team Red.
Welcome!
- I'm here.
- You have 100 million diamonds.
- Yes.
- I'll take 75 million.
Now I can hand these out.
- Is this correct?
- Yes.
Everyone's relocating,
so it's 62.5 million.
I have 12 million diamonds left.
This goes to Blue now.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Good, it's all set. Everything's in order.
Since I can run the Platform,
I can distribute the lives, credits,
and diamonds equally
according to their interests.
We put 25,000 dollars in Team White...
to use for the war and weapon costs.
Team Red has the most people,
so they get 62,500 dollars.
That leaves Team Blue with 12,500 dollars.
- Now you can start a war.
- Okay.
Now, let's go and tell...
- It's time.
- all the Blues to relocate to Red.
- Should we talk here?
- What?
- Let's do that.
- Sure.
- Should I bring the others?
- Thanks.
Okay.
Maillard said he'll be here
after a quick talk too.
- Is everyone here?
- Yes.
Maetel, there's...
Mokgye is out there...
with a great sense of leadership.
She brought all the Red members together.
She wanted to talk with everyone,
so we're all meeting at the Hub.
She's trying everything right now?
Yes, She even cried down there earlier.
- Right. I understand.
- I really want to support her.
- Let's go and back her up.
- Sure.
I was a little out of it,
and she scolded me.
Okay, let's do it.
Just standing by her will be enough.
- Hello.
- There's not a lot of space,
- but should we start talking?
- Of course.
- We can just stand here.
- Sure.
- Reboot!
- Yes?
Did I see you already today?
- Hi.
- It felt like the first time.
Right? It's good to see you.
So even until last night, we thought...
we were on the same boat as Team Red.
That's what we thought.
But during the leader negotiations,
we noticed some other nuances...
- You noticed it. Yes.
- from the others.
And we concluded that...
- our offer wasn't enticing enough.
- Okay.
I'm going to make a personal offer.
We'll give you 80 percent of what we have.
Eighty percent. This is a great offer.
- Even if we take a little,
- Yes?
- we want to win.
- Yes.
We're thirsty for victory.
I did act arbitrarily.
But I thought some spontaneity...
was what we needed
to break this fixed situation.
I think it was a way
for us to tell Team Red...
that we're willing to change
and make this offer...
and appeal to them.
- It's not a bad deal for you.
- Of course.
- You're not here to make friends.
- Sure.
Then be reasonable about this.
You're going to turn this offer down...
just because
you spent five days with them?
But are you making this offer...
after you've all reached an agreement?
No, this was just my idea.
You're just throwing it out there?
- If I may...
- Go ahead.
I would like to support her.
Okay, Ugong is on board.
I guess you came to talk with us...
because it'll take too long
to talk among yourselves.
What are we up to now?
(Maillard arrived after the trade.)
- Should I get another umbrella?
- Thanks.
- It's pouring out here.
- Right.
It's showering suddenly.
I'll head inside for a while
since it's raining so much.
You should stay.
No, I'll go with you.
We'll go together.
What is she trying to do?
There's nothing we can do right now.
But we still need to reach an agreement.
This is so sudden.
We don't know how many people...
- like that offer or don't.
- Right.
She can't just bulldoze her way
into this without talking to us.
It makes those four hours of us
talking here meaningless.
I wanted to lay low for the day...
and let her talk on her own.
Then I wanted to deliver a blow tomorrow,
but now it's over.
Now, we won't have moves to make tomorrow.
Our plan was to wait for another day.
- Yes, for tomorrow.
- Exactly.
We were going to look for a chance.
But Mokgye thinks differently.
She thinks we need to step up
and try anything in this situation.
- But...
- She's entitled to her own opinions,
but she can't present
that idea like it was the team's.
She didn't say that.
We were all standing next to her.
I agree with you on that, Reboot.
But I told her she has my support.
I'm trying to say
that we must have grounds.
Why is she going against
what we all talked about together?
We thought we had
all reached an agreement,
but Mokgye never agreed to it.
I think she wants to try out her idea now.
She should've done that individually.
We're bound as a team,
so she has no choice.
I think she was frustrated.
She wanted to try something on her own,
but when she brought it up,
we turned it down
for this and that reason.
- But this sort of behavior...
- Yes?
- makes things difficult internally.
- You're right.
But please let this one slide.
Reboot was upset
she spoke about something...
that wasn't agreed upon as a team.
One side is focusing on the procedure,
but the other side wants to take action.
Yet, we're all in the same team,
so I'm torn.
But regarding the issue, I thought...
Mokgye's impulsive decision
to break the status quo...
was vaild.
Maillard, I'll summarize things for you.
Mokgye wanted to
break through this situation,
and she offered
to share 80 percent of their gold.
And we should make a blood alliance.
Please adopt me as your daughter.
Or how about them?
But you've never responded
to our offers...
with sincerity before.
I thought those misunderstandings...
and the dragging conversation
were the problem.
Anyway, that's our offer.
I'd like for you to give us an answer now.
But we need to talk to the other team.
You called us first,
but they're grilling me
about giving you the diamonds.
I'm stuck between two teams.
I'm being questioned by White,
and now Gold wants
to make a blood alliance.
But that's just what Red is right now.
- It can't be helped.
- But if you think differently,
- any team that sides with you...
- Right, it's up to us.
gets to win this.
- Really?
- Yes.
Then why are you pressuring us?
- Red is definitely winning.
- Then we...
- offer 80 percent...
- Yesterday, we...
We said we were supporting Gold yesterday.
- You said nothing yesterday!
- But that was...
And now you want to make a blood alliance?
I already offered to be your adopted son!
Now you want to be our daughter?
I already did this yesterday!
- This was me!
- I...
- Please get up.
- Well...
- Stand up.
- That...
That was really...
a misjudgment on my part.
It's not too late for you to be adopted.
- We...
- Then...
are you talking about relocation?
What are you offering exactly?
An exchange of one person each.
Who are we exchanging?
It doesn't matter.
- I'd like to go, honestly.
- Yes?
I've wanted to work
with you for a while now.
Then Ugong will relocate to our team.
What's going to happen
based on these conditions?
A blood alliance.
We want reassurance that
you'll choose Gold at the end.
Then we promise you 80 percent.
- Eighty percent of your gold?
- Yes.
Exactly.
Okay.
I'm intrigued.
This is an offer you can't refuse.
But during negotiations,
it's best for you to have counteroffers.
That's why our offer is appealing to you.
When they hear we're friendly,
other teams might offer you a bigger cut.
Either way, Team Red gets the prize money,
no matter what.
The question is how much you'll get.
You might have to share with them.
But since we're offering 80 percent,
they might offer 90 percent in return.
Whatever the case,
this isn't a bad deal for you.
And we're being open about that.
I don't think I can
give you an answer right now.
They need to check with Reboot too.
- No, it's...
- Reboot will be okay.
It's not just that. He's the leader.
- He has a say...
- It's just one vote.
He's alone.
Our official decision is to go with this.
- With four votes, it's official.
- Yes.
- All right.
- Give us some time.
We can't really decide anything right now.
- Right.
- Come back later.
Just a moment.
- I hope you make a good decision.
- We won't keep you waiting.
Thanks for the offer.
Thank you.
I have a question.
- When you said 80 percent...
- Yes?
- I was...
- Is that from now?
- Or from the final?
- No, but...
eighty percent of what we have now.
Was that number agreed upon?
No.
- Actually...
- Why did you bring up a number?
- Reboot told me...
- Yes.
- he wasn't happy with this.
- Because of the percentage.
I was a little flustered too.
But it's a conversation starter.
It's 80 percent of our gold now,
but I think...
- Let's go in first.
- I think we can talk to them later.
So we give them
80 percent of the valuation now.
- If we issue more gold,
- Yes, 80 percent of now.
- the valuation will drop.
- Yes, we can issue more.
But if we issue gold after this,
we'd be betraying them.
I'm fine with 80 percent.
Let's see if they take our offer.
If they don't even accept
this amazing offer,
we'll think of the next step.
We have nothing without change now!
That's why I made an extreme decision.
I'll take responsibility.
I won't take the prize money.
I'm guessing the problem is
with the ratio.
I won't take my cut.
This isn't about the prize.
We're in a team here.
I understand you might be upset.
It's not about feelings either.
It might've been a miscommunication,
but Ugong first came up to us...
and asked us to just listen to
what you had to say.
That's why I went.
But you already decided on
a percentage of 80...
and made it seem like an official offer.
If I'd known that, I wouldn't have gone.
It's been only five days...
since we got here.
And I couldn't stand
the thought of not doing anything...
during our remaining time here.
That's why I already said
those who think so...
can do whatever you can individually.
But we really needed a change.
Yes, we know. We've talked about it.
But to bring about change,
we need to make impulsive decisions.
Otherwise, it'll be the same.
You understand
we're not part of your own team, Mokgye.
- Of course.
- Right?
- Then...
- I'm just a member.
We reached
a decision not to do anything...
through a lot of debate and conversation.
Things are bad as is.
Did you really have to make things harder?
Not taking action
would've made things harder.
- So...
- I'm not against taking action.
- Yes. But I think...
- There is a process to this...
Could I step in for a second?
I understand everything you've said.
There is the issue of the procedure,
and the ratio was a bit of a gamble.
This is how I took this.
We didn't get to reappoint
the leader because I wasn't here.
I think Mokgye wanted
to be the leader too.
I do feel bad to Reboot for saying this,
but I supported Mokgye...
as a way to start tomorrow a bit early.
This is a survival show.
It'll be great
to have everything by procedure.
But in this situation,
we have to play it by ear...
and respond to a sudden action...
from time to time.
I'd like to say something.
Things were already bad.
But acting on her own
without talking to us first...
was a mistake on Mokgye's part,
and she admitted it too.
What I don't want is
our team to split into two.
When we're divided,
we're going to start arguing.
It'll be like who's on Reboot's side,
and who's on Mokgye's side.
And if we start...
splitting up into groups as a team,
it'll ultimately come back to bite us.
I want to move on to the next step.
So all we do is wait for the moment?
There's nothing we can do?
Paul of Team Blue
has relocated to Team Red.
Paul, please go to your dormitory
within an hour.
- They're turning our offer down.
- Right.
This is...
Paul of Team Blue
has relocated to Team Red.
This is interesting.
So they're turning it down.
Even an offer of 80 percent!
But why? What did they offer?
Staying inside right now is really bad.
The other teams are communicating...
to convince each other...
and make offers.
- It doesn't matter now.
- Then let's go over to Red.
We can ask them...
why they made this decision.
Siseon of Team Blue...
- has relocated to Team Red.
- Who?
Siseon is going to Red too.
So they're bonding like this.
They're doing exactly
what we offered them.
They might've gotten a higher cut.
That's true.
- Didn't you see this coming?
- No, we did.
- This was to be expected.
- Yes.
It's true that there's been a change...
because we went out and took action.
We have to keep stirring the pot...
to find a crack for us to enter through.
- What if it brings them closer?
- That could happen.
But I think shaking things up is
needed to find the fissure.
I disagree.
We wouldn't be in this situation
if we had stayed still.
He's right too.
- If we didn't do anything...
- They wouldn't have taken action.
Exactly.
So they're copying us
now that we made the move.
I'd like to make a suggestion...
since the dynamics have changed.
They have five people now.
That means they have at least five lives.
We should go in before
the trade is over and start a war.
(Start a war.)
- What if they...
- Wait.
only relocated without the lives?
It's better for us
if they didn't take lives with them.
If we slash them in half
before they bring their lives,
one of them has to go home today.
- That's good. Let's do that.
- Yes.
(Trading session)
This is Leia, Team White's leader.
We wanted to
live peacefully with Team Gold,
the new members of our community.
We wanted to cooperate
and live a life without war.
But that didn't go as we planned.
We wanted to avoid war at all costs,
regardless of the reason.
I know this is all an excuse.
But I wanted to...
save everyone in Team White.
Team White declares war on Team Gold.
Today's war cost is 200 diamonds.
Write the amount on the voucher...
and submit it through the central box.
I paid the war cost of 200 diamonds.
The war cost has been paid.
(Team White has declared war
on Team Gold.)
Team White has declared war on Team Gold.
Community Town now enters a state of war.
- Well...
- Someone started a war.
Team White has declared war on Team Gold.
White declared it on us.
They put all their resources to Red...
or gave them to Black
for White to do this.
I know. We had to declare war first.
We could've eliminated them,
and now we're late again.
Compared to them,
our decision-making process is
too long and slow.
That's why they always get to us.
I was frustrated.
We had to make contact
and talk to other teams...
to persuade them.
But we always take so long
talking and planning among ourselves.
We lose time and miss opportunities.
It's a shame.
Up until now,
they pretended not to be seen as a team.
But now they're making it clear
they've allied together.
So there was a change.
I still don't know why they had to
declare war against us.
Did they not have enough lives
to make it past today?
But my calculations say otherwise.
If they're joining as one team,
three teams don't need lives.
I wouldn't be upset if they had
a valid reason for this war.
But as of now,
I can't see any reason for this.
I'm just so confused.
We are in a state of war.
All residents,
please go to your dormitory...
- and wait for further instructions.
- This is insane.
Yesterday, my identity was revealed,
as was Donkey's.
Then Maillard
and the weapon dealer join hands.
Leia, who lost a precious teammate
because of the weapon dealer,
joined hands
with the weapon dealer as well.
They've been at each other's throats,
but I guess they needed
some money in the end.
Come in.
(Dormitory for Red)
- Is this your first time here?
- It is.
I haven't had a chance.
So...
We won't have to produce...
credits or anything, right?
I'm not sure.
But we need to make a choice.
There will be
only one production site tomorrow anyway.
I'd like to win this war...
and see what resources they have.
Then I want to make a bid...
for an appropriate amount.
- We gave them so many resources.
- Right.
If they'd offered that...
when I went to the Center yesterday,
I would've taken it.
They might've won this...
- if they had made that decision...
- Right.
- and negotiated with us.
- Yes.
Right now, we have to fight in a war...
that we are not prepared for.
But I really want us to pull through.
At this point,
winning is our only option.
- Let's fight for our deaths.
- But would Leia win...
- if she went against us alone?
- No, wait.
- They teamed up.
- Her alliance is there.
- It's 6 to 5.
- Yes, it's 6 to 5.
We still have a shot at this.
We need to decide
if we're buying weapons now.
I don't think
it's a good idea to use weapons.
We'd just be giving
either Vector or Donkey the money.
It'll be better
not to play into their hands.
- Let's win this.
- Now that this is happening today,
- let's give it our all and do this.
- Yes.
Purchasing weapons
and forming alliances...
in a state of war is possible now.
Let's go.
Please visit the Center...
- if you would like to purchase weapons.
- Go.
- Let's go!
- Okay.
This is a lightning war. Darn it.
Let's just head there, just in case.
Yes, we'll see how they play things.
If you would like to form an alliance,
ring the bell in your dormitory...
to contact the other team.
I request an alliance with Team Red.
Quickly!
Gosh.
- We have to accept the alliance.
- Where is everyone?
Why are you all so fast?
Oh, I can't see the weapon cost...
because I'm not in this war.
I'm not of use. They have to get here.
Leia!
- Yes?
- Come out.
I requested an alliance.
You have to accept first.
Don't weapons come first?
- Purchase weapons first?
- Yes.
Weapons? Did anyone come out?
No, they're not here.
Hurry.
What's taking her so long?
There's no rush, but still.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
I guess you're experienced
in a state of war.
Shall we?
I'm glad everyone's energized now.
I like playing games like this.
I'm a warlord now.
(The diamond alliance arrives
at the Center first.)
Warlord Leia.
(State of War, Purchasing weapons,
Forming alliances)
Team White will purchase weapons.
Please check the weapon cost...
and tell us the class of weapons
you'd like to purchase.
It's 12 million, 8 million,
and five million. That's right.
I will purchase
all three classes of weapons.
You have selected
Class A, Class B, and Class C weapons.
Please submit the voucher
in the central box.
I'm sorry, but I need to make sure...
we win this war.
I'm purchasing all of them.
(25 million diamonds)
The weapon cost has been paid.
Please collect the weapons
from the central box.
Come on, we're all new to this,
and we're all older.
- Take it easy on us.
- We're not so young ourselves.
Sweetie, we gave birth too.
- I can't compete with that.
- Yes, we're parents.
Paul, come in.
Was the weapon cost set as we calculated?
Yes, about 25 million diamonds.
- Minus 200 diamonds.
- Right.
Team White and Team Red
will form an alliance.
have formed an alliance.
- Now, the two teams...
- Let's do this.
- will fight the war together.
- Yes!
Great.
I think we'll win.
We have all three weapons.
And the headcount is
different from the first war.
We have one more member.
I know the initiator
shouldn't feel this way.
It's so hypocritical.
But I do feel sorry.
I wonder how high...
- the cost is.
- Right?
We would like to check the weapon cost.
- All weapons have been purchased.
- Eighty quintillion gold.
There are no weapons remaining.
Eighty quintillion?
- This is hilarious.
- It's so funny.
I think they tried...
to meet the amount.
- If it was distributed fairly,
- Yes.
- They must've met the amount.
- that's the amount...
going to the weapon dealer.
They're looking after Vector and Donkey.
Just wipe us out.
We're already getting wiped out.
If you're trying to wipe us out,
we'll play along.
Let's have some fun.
- It's chilly.
- Yes.
- It was hot last time we were here.
- I know.
- It's the rain.
- Right.
Who has weapons A, B, and C?
- Maillard.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
I can't believe we're back here.
(Battlefield)
What is this?
What's that?
OX?
- It's the OX quiz.
- The OX quiz.
Isn't this a gavel?
- Wait, Luna. Was it done here?
- Yes.
- Is it the same place?
(Exclaiming)
It reminds me of "Gonjiam."
It looks like an OX quiz.
It says Team Gold versus Team White.
Are we playing an OX quiz?
They look like they'd be good at it.
It was more organized than the first time.
I guess it's a quiz.
I thought it wouldn't be in my favor.
Because everyone in Team Gold is...
good at games.
That game is worth playing.
I'm the best at it.
There's no psychological pressure.
Today's battle is...
the Fact Land Grab.
- Fact.
- Fact Land Grab.
- Land Grab.
- We have a journalist.
- Good.
We have someone who deals with facts
in front of us.
In the Fact Land Grab,
you'll answer O or X...
for the 49 questions on common sense
on the question board.
You must take more spots.
You'll play a total of three rounds.
Here are the keywords for each round.
Round One, politics and economy.
Round Two, cultural industries.
Round Three, general knowledge.
We got this.
It'll be much easier for her...
since it's her field.
Only one person from each team
will play per round.
The same resident can play
more than two rounds.
Once the round begins,
the question board will be revealed.
The question board consists
of 45 questions...
and four question marks.
The question marks will be relocated
in every round.
If you choose the question mark,
a random effect will take place.
After the question is revealed,
you'll be given a minute
to come up with a strategy.
After one minute, whoever goes first...
will receive 15 seconds
to choose the question.
And 30 seconds to put down the OX cubes...
and submit the answer.
If the answer is correct,
the land becomes the answerer's land.
And you may continue
to choose the question.
If the answer is incorrect,
the land becomes the opponent's land.
And the opponent gets to play next.
If you exceed the time limit,
the opponent gets to play next
with no other penalties.
Is it better to let the opponent play
instead of getting it wrong?
- We shouldn't answer what we don't know.
- Choosing questions is important,
as well as the person who has to solve it.
If one team forms a line...
whether it's horizontal, vertical,
or diagonal,
the resident of that team...
can immediately take over
one of the opponents' land.
Once all the land is colored,
the round ends.
The team with bigger land...
wins the round.
And the team that wins
first 2 rounds out of 3...
becomes the winner of the war today.
Before the game begins,
both leaders will participate in the match
to decide who goes first.
The leader who wins the match...
can choose which round...
to go first between Rounds 1 and 2.
The leader who loses in the match...
gets to start the round
the other team didn't choose.
For Round Three,
the team with bigger land
after combining Rounds 1 and 2...
gets to play first.
When I saw the name, Fact Land Grab,
I heard someone behind me going,
"We have a journalist
who deals with facts."
Round One was about politics and economy.
Round Two was about cultural industries.
Round Three was general knowledge.
To be honest,
it doesn't matter to me.
It might be pretty tough...
because I assumed Team Gold...
had many players who were experts.
This is going to be fun.
We will have a chance.
They're good at quizzes.
They're all smart people.
One person will come up to compete...
in each round.
In terms of numbers or physique,
we're second to none.
It might actually be worth trying.
That's what came to my mind.
Good luck.
(Both leaders participate in the match
to decide who goes first.)
- Let's go.
- You got this.
Now, we will start a match
to decide who goes first.
Here is the question.
(The Disease Control and Prevention Agency
says bright clothes prevent mosquitoes.)
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
(The two leaders have different answers
from the start.)
The answer is O.
(Team White gets to decide
when to go first.)
That's okay.
I guessed it.
- Good job.
- That was a trap.
That's the momentum.
That's right. You're doing great.
They get to choose when to go first.
It doesn't matter, right?
For Round One,
we don't know how hard questions might be.
While trying to answer them,
we might lose the pace.
After Round One, we might get the idea.
Playing first in Round Two...
- That makes sense.
- will help us...
- I agree with you.
- build experience.
- It's better to go first in Round Two.
- Okay.
Honestly, you know politics and economy...
- better than anyone else.
- But...
just because I write critiques
doesn't mean I know the facts.
Honestly,
I'm not an economist.
I thought half of it
would be about the economy.
It was kind of pressuring.
I also worked on the quiz...
to decide who would go first.
So I thought someone else should try it.
I think Reboot...
will play in Round One.
Don't expect him to do well.
- Okay.
- He's right.
- Then we'll go with what we're good at.
- I can play too.
- I'm going to turn the tables.
- Okay.
- Then I'll play in Round 1.
- You can play in Round 1.
- Okay.
- Since you're a journalist.
We're starting with politics and economy.
To be honest,
I want to play general knowledge.
But don't you watch YouTube
about politics a lot?
- You'd be good at it.
- You want me to play in Round 1?
- Play in Round 1.
It's general knowledge
about politics and the economy.
If you watched the news or YouTube a lot,
- You'll be good at it.
- you'd know the answer.
I don't watch the news.
- Give it a try.
- Me neither.
Then...
I'll give it a try.
Anyone other than the resident
who is playing in Round One,
please move to the viewing zone.
I'm getting nervous.
- Let's win!
- This is going to be fun.
- Let's win.
(Viewing zone)
- This is crazy.
- Crazy? What's crazy?
- Why?
(Exclaiming)
This is spooky.
- That's what I mean.
- What is this?
The residents
who are playing in Round One,
please go to your spots.
I'm actually...
learning from your YouTube.
This is not in my favor.
No.
Oftentimes, journalists have...
wide but shallow knowledge.
I've already known her before coming here.
I'm learning politics and economy...
from her YouTube.
I'm basically going up against my teacher.
I couldn't help...
but think,
"Is this even worth trying?"
I heard Ugong...
works as an oriental doctor.
He's also very good at survival games.
I heard he's highly interested
in current affairs.
Of course, I was worried.
I was very nervous.
The keyword...
of Fact Land Grab Round One is...
politics and economy.
They must be so nervous.
- It's not like I'm playing,
- That's what I mean.
- but I'm getting so nervous.
- I want to pee all of a sudden.
You'll have a minute to check
the questions.
After one minute, the team going first
will choose the question.
(Round 1, Politics and economy)
Oh, that's hard.
- We get to see all the questions.
- That's what I mean.
The ones in the middle aren't revealed
until they choose it.
You should've played instead.
- Izaha, you know them, right?
- They're pretty good questions.
- Too many of them are on economy.
- Yes.
I know.
They're hard.
The participating residents must return
the writing supplies and paper.
What?
We can only watch.
In case they have the answers
written down?
From now on, let's begin...
Fact Land Grab Round One.
After the whistle, Team Gold,
who is playing first,
must choose a question.
I choose B1.
(GDP includes the value of household work
that is not traded in the market.)
Correct.
I choose D1.
(Income tax is an indirect tax.)
Income tax is an indirect tax.
X.
Correct.
I choose E7.
(Opportunity cost is the value of the best
alternative that you give up...)
(when you make a choice.)
That's true.
Correct.
I'll use Class C Weapon.
(I'll use Class C Weapon.)
- Already?
- She's taking the turn.
Team Gold's turn is handed over
to Team White.
You know three-cushion billiards?
Global players can get dozens of points...
in a single turn.
That's what might happen.
So I decided to...
make a decision at the beginning.
I used Class C Weapon...
and took the turn.
I choose C3.
(The President appoints the Speaker
of the National Assembly.)
X.
Correct.
I choose D3.
(The trickle-down effect
is a theory that says...)
(growth among large corporations
and wealthy people...)
(will eventually benefit ordinary people.)
O.
Correct.
It's her specialty.
I choose E3.
(A majority vote of
the Constitutional Court justices...)
(is required for an impeachment decision.)
X.
Correct.
- She's taking the lead with politics.
- Politics.
She's taking the lead with politics.
Keep going.
I choose C4.
(Judicial independence means ensuring
that judges make decisions...)
(according to
the President's instructions.)
That's X.
X.
Correct.
I choose C2.
(A local council has the authority
to discuss and approve the budget...)
(of the local government.)
O.
Correct.
I choose E2.
(The Prosecutor General can be impeached.)
O.
Correct.
I choose F1.
(Quantitative easing is a policy in which
the central bank injects money...)
(into the economy.)
Quantitative easing is a policy...
O.
Correct.
- She's so good and calm.
- Keep it up.
I choose G1.
(Stagflation is a phenomenon in which
economic stagnation and rising prices...)
(occur simultaneously.)
O.
Correct.
I choose D5.
- X.
- Correct.
She's on a roll.
I choose D6.
- X.
- Correct.
I choose D7.
There goes my teacher.
(Ugong, Oriental doctor)
It's unlikely for me to win this game...
because she answered
many of the questions...
that I'd know.
So every time she answered one,
I groaned internally.
My glimmers of hope were disappearing.
I got the feeling
the candles were going out.
X.
(In a citizen-participation trial,
the jury's verdict is legally binding.)
Correct.
- She's matchless.
- That's what I mean.
That's awesome.
She's good.
No wonder she's a political journalist.
X.
- Correct.
- Good job.
- That's crazy.
- Awesome.
Leia is crazy good!
Gosh.
Correct.
O.
She doesn't even make a mistake.
That's...
She's starting to get confused.
I choose F7.
(The Constitutional Court
consists of nine judges.)
O.
Correct.
(20 answers in a row)
"When the exchange rate falls,
import prices also fall."
Economy is easy but confusing.
Just five more, and we win.
Four, three,
- Hurry up.
- two...
I choose B3.
(When inflation occurs,
the value of money rises...)
(while the value of goods falls.)
X.
Correct.
(Inflation reduces the value of money.)
Four more to go.
- If she answers four more...
- That's more than half.
- More than half?
- That ends the game.
It's critical that we can't play.
Complementary...
No, she's better off not answering.
I choose A5.
Time out.
That was close. It's okay.
- It's actually better.
- At least she didn't get it wrong.
(If she gets it wrong,
the opponent takes their land.)
Team Gold's turn.
I choose F4.
(Individuals can freely choose...)
(whether to enroll
in the National Health Insurance program.)
X.
Correct.
(National Health Insurance is
mandatory for all citizens.)
I choose G4.
(The Constitution guarantees labor unions
the right to collective bargaining.)
Correct.
I choose A3.
(A progressive tax system applies
lower tax rates to people...)
(with higher incomes
in order to promote fairness.)
A progressive tax...
X.
Correct.
(A progressive tax system
applies higher tax rates...)
(to people with higher incomes.)
I choose C5.
(Issuing government bonds
increases government debt.)
It increases
when government bonds are issued.
Correct.
I choose G6.
(The United Kingdom was the first country
in the world...)
(to grant women the right to vote.)
Correct.
(New Zealand was the first country
to grant women the right to vote.)
I choose A5.
(Under the current presidential system,)
(the President has the authority
to dissolve the National Assembly.)
X.
Correct.
(The President's power to dissolve
the National Assembly has been abolished.)
I'm not sure.
- Now...
- Now it's getting hard.
- It's starting to get confusing.
- Yes.
- There are still question marks.
- They can try the question marks.
I choose A7.
(The voting age is 19.)
O.
Incorrect.
(A7 is handed over to Team White
as the answer is wrong.)
- Wrong.
- Is it 18?
- He said 19.
Three more to go.
I'm doomed.
Team White's turn.
I choose G5.
(Constitutional Court judges serve
6-year terms and may be reappointed.)
X.
Incorrect.
That's okay.
- It's kind of hard.
- Team Gold's turn.
I choose F3.
(The 5 permanent members
of the UN Security Council are...)
(the US, the UK, France, China,
and South Korea.)
X.
Correct.
(They are the US, the UK, France, China,
and Russia.)
I choose G3.
(The Chief Justice of the Supreme Court
of Korea is appointed by the President...)
(with the consent
of the National Assembly.)
O.
Correct.
I choose C6.
(GDP is the total value produced
within a country's territory.)
O.
Correct.
I choose C1.
(When calculating the unemployment rate,
people who have given up...)
(looking for work are included
in the labor force.)
- X.
- They aren't included.
Correct.
(4 answers in a row)
Give us one now.
Someone has to try D four now.
Time out.
Team White's turn.
I choose C7.
(The term invisible hand was first used
by Adam Smith in "The Wealth of Nations.")
O.
Incorrect.
My gosh.
Team Gold's turn.
I think the title of the book is wrong.
But I'm not sure.
He's torn.
Time out.
Time to open the question mark.
It's okay to try the question mark
when you're stuck.
I choose G7.
(In Korea, citizen participation trials
are held only in criminal cases.)
O.
Correct.
I choose B7.
"When the exchange rate falls,
import prices also fall."
The exchange rate, okay. It has to fall.
O.
Correct.
- Our leader is amazing.
- That's what I mean.
- Good job.
- She's my leader.
- But we...
- Are you a spy?
(1 more question
until getting 25 questions)
I choose B4.
(Minority shareholder rights are rights
that can be exercised...)
(by any shareholder
who owns even a single share.)
O.
I'm not sure about that.
Minority shareholder rights must be
something else.
Incorrect.
(In some cases, shareholders must own
a certain percentage of shares.)
Team Gold's turn.
(If Team Gold gets it wrong,
Team White gets more than half.)
I choose G2.
(WHO is a specialized agency of the UN,
headquartered in Manhattan, New York.)
This has to be guessed.
Incorrect.
It's hard now.
(Team White secured more than half.)
- That's a relief.
- It's okay to open the center now.
Team White's turn.
Go for D four.
I choose A4.
(Goods that provide greater utility
when consumed together,)
(such as coffee and sugar, are called
complementary goods.)
O.
Correct.
Did we make it?
There's obviously more white.
We have to get as many questions
as possible...
So it's favorable for us...
- in the next round.
- That too.
I choose E6.
O.
Correct.
(The UN Secretary-General is appointed
by the General Assembly...)
(upon the recommendation
of the Security Council.)
I choose A6.
(The closer the Gini coefficient is to 1,
the more equal the income distribution.)
O.
Incorrect.
(The closer it is to 1,
the greater the income inequality.)
Now it's time for the question mark.
They only have the question marks left.
I choose B2.
(Tactical support, counts as correct)
Oh, there was a bonus.
- Right.
- It's a bonus.
What?
It's a bonus.
- It's never easy.
- That means there's also a dud.
I choose F2.
- A mine.
- If there's a bonus, there's also a dud.
- That's right.
I'm stuck.
Neither of us can make a bingo.
Still, I stopped you.
I choose B6.
(Tactical support, counts as correct)
Okay.
I choose D4.
(The law
of diminishing marginal utility states...)
(that as the consumption
of a good increases,)
(the satisfaction gained from
each additional unit also increases.)
The law of diminishing marginal utility...
- No, it's the opposite!
- increases... No.
X.
Correct.
(The remaining square is a question mark.)
- Stay still.
- Relax.
I choose F6.
What?
- Why did you do that?
- What's wrong with you?
You should have waited.
There are 2 good squares
and 2 bad squares.
Round One of Fact Land Grab has ended.
The result will be announced.
Team Gold earned 19 points,
and Team White earned 30 points.
Team White won the first round.
- Thank you for your work.
- You're so good.
- I used the weapon. I think that's why.
Actually, I think Ugong
knows the answers...
to the questions I answered today.
But as I used Stealing the Turn,
I seized the initiative early on,
and that gave me
a huge advantage, I guess.
I felt sorry for my team members,
but what could I do? She was good.
She was out of my league.
I need to cheer so that our team can do
a good job in the second round.
Residents who compete in the second round,
please go to the battlefield.
I have no clue
about the cultural industries.
Cultural industries means...
It's about music and musical, and so on.
Payment amount, sales...
It could be in my favor since I hosted
"B-Side Economics."
Among the other team members,
I don't think there are many people...
- who know about the cultural industries.
- Right. I guess they're not aware.
I think I can do a good job.
- I know.
- What topics would come up?
Just corporations and all.
- You're interested in those topics.
- Semiconductors. I know.
And Maetel has a quick wit.
For now, we...
Residents who compete in the second round,
please go to your spots.
The keyword for the second round
is cultural industries.
Actually, my major is
business and economics,
so I was more fit for the first round.
Still, I view
culture-related elements broadly...
from an industrial perspective,
so I was confident.
I thought I could do a good job, at first.
I thought I stood a good chance
if it was about culture.
Guessing it together and doing it alone
feels totally different.
I think Maetel will do a good job.
She has good intuition.
You will have one minute to check
the layout of the questions.
In one minute, the first group
will start choosing questions.
(Round 2, Cultural Industries)
- I'm sure she will be good.
- She will do an excellent job.
This is just for Izaha.
I know a lot of them here.
It is difficult, though.
It's what "B-Side Economics" deals with.
Some of them are tricky.
Now, Round Two of Fact Land Grab begins.
When the whistle blows,
Team White, the first group,
can choose a question.
I choose A1.
I think Izaha will do a good job too.
Correct.
I choose B2.
Krafton, a Korean company.
(Battlegrounds was developed
by an American game company.)
Correct.
I choose D3.
(Netflix originally started
as a DVD mail-rental service.)
Correct.
I choose A5.
(Spotify is a music streaming service
created by an American company.)
Correct.
- Is it false? How does he know that?
- He's unbelievable.
He knows everything.
I choose B7.
(Nintendo has made video games from
the very beginning of its foundation.)
- Correct.
- The company made Japanese playing cards.
Japanese playing cards?
I choose F5.
(Minecraft is a game developed
by Microsoft.)
You shouldn't say it's true.
Does he know something more accurate?
Correct.
Mojang is the right answer.
Mojang developed it originally.
Microsoft owns it now.
I choose E7.
Correct.
I choose G2.
I choose E1.
Correct.
I choose C1.
He's competent. Izaha is competent.
Correct.
(10 answers in a row)
I choose F4.
(The first Disneyland theme park
was built in Orlando, Florida.)
Isn't it false? It's false.
- Incorrect.
- Oh, my.
- Where is it?
- It's false. It's in California.
The biggest one is in Orlando.
Team Gold's turn.
A2.
(YouTube Shorts were launched
before Instagram Reels.)
They were not launched before.
Reels were launched before that.
Correct.
I choose A7.
She's an expert in this field.
She used to work at Netflix.
Disney Plus was launched later.
It's false.
- Correct.
- The right member was chosen.
I choose B5.
Amazon took over Twitch.
Correct.
G5.
(The lyrics of BTS's first Billboard No. 1
song, "Dynamite." are all in English.)
Correct.
It's all written in English.
I didn't know.
I choose C4.
(Instagram is a social media platform
operated by Meta.)
O.
Correct.
F6.
Ministry of Culture, Sports, and Tourism?
It's false.
It's Korea Media and Communications
Standards Commission.
(In South Korea, MCST has the authority
to review broadcasting content.)
Correct.
He solved questions she could have
answered before she got a chance.
I choose C7.
(NFTs proves ownership of digital assets
based on blockchain technology.)
O.
She's so composed.
Correct.
I choose B1.
(QR codes originated
from a Japanese company.)
O.
Correct.
I choose C3.
- It's false.
- Correct.
Tokyo isn't one of those cities.
- She's good.
- She's amazing.
(10 versus 10, 9 correct answers in a row)
I choose F2.
It's not France.
- Correct.
- Spain.
I choose G6.
(The number of YouTube Premium users
worldwide has surpassed 100 million.)
Does 100 million have 8 zeros?
One...
I guess she's confused about the number.
It has surpassed.
- Correct.
- She knows details.
I choose E5.
(South Korea's Pansori is listed
as a UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage.)
It is listed.
- She's awesome.
- Correct.
Isn't Maetel a foreigner?
How come she knows these things so well?
I choose G7.
("Parasite" is the first Korean film to be
invited to the Cannes Film Festival.)
It's false.
("Parasite" is the first Korean film to be
invited to the Cannes Film Festival.)
Correct.
("The Wheel" by Director Lee Doo Yong
is the first film.)
I choose E2.
(Copyright is automatically created
the moment a work is made,)
(and no separate registration process
is required.)
It is required.
Incorrect.
- Nice.
- This is difficult.
It's really difficult.
It's time to strike back.
Team White's turn.
I choose B4.
(All terrestrial broadcasters in Korea can
air general commercial advertisements.)
X.
Can't EBS do that?
Correct.
(EBS prohibits commercial advertisements.)
I choose D5.
(The first e-sports stadium
in South Korea was built in Busan.)
O.
Incorrect.
It's Seoul.
(The first e-sports stadium
was built in Yongsan, Seoul.)
Team Gold's turn.
I choose A4.
Yes!
She is a risk-taker.
Choosing a question mark
requires great courage.
She's very composed.
I choose C6.
(As of 2026, Michael Jackson's "Thriller"
is listed...)
(as the best-selling album
in Guinness World Records.)
It's false.
Incorrect.
It looks like things are a bit risky.
I choose D4.
No, it's from science.
It's false.
Correct.
(The term was first coined by
evolutionary biologist Richard Dawkins.)
I choose F7.
(The Nobel Prize in Literature is selected
from works published in that year.)
It's false.
Correct.
(It is awarded to the author,
not to a specific work.)
It's confusing.
I choose A6.
(The same founding brothers established
the sports brands Adidas and Puma.)
O.
Correct.
Both have a massive amount
of general knowledge.
I choose C5.
- NBA. It should be Michael Jordan.
- I think it's true.
I count on you, Brother Jordan.
- Incorrect.
- Goodness.
It's false?
It's before him. Isn't it Jerry West?
Team Gold's turn.
I choose D1.
Please.
Yes!
- What? That's insane.
- Luck is on her side.
Then the remaining two
must be marked as incorrect answers.
Right. There's a high probability
they're wrong.
She shouldn't pick those.
D6.
O.
(The Louvre Museum was originally built
and used as a royal palace.)
Correct.
I choose G1.
(Literary works' copyright is protected
for 50 years after the author's death.)
X.
Correct.
I choose D2.
(South Korea's screen quota system
was abolished after the Korea-US FTA.)
O.
- Incorrect.
- That's a relief.
(The quota has been reduced
but is still in effect.)
Aren't they pretty neck and neck
right now?
Let me think about it a little more.
- That's nice.
- Time out.
That's a good idea.
Now, he's looking through the sentences
one by one more carefully.
I choose E6.
(Lim Yun Chan was the youngest winner of
the 2022 Van Cliburn Piano Competition.)
O.
- She has the heart of a beast.
- Correct.
- Nice.
- She's good.
I choose B6.
One is a palm tree,
and the other is a lion.
I think one of them represents Venice.
It's a little tricky.
It could be a different film festival.
- It's really confusing.
- X.
Incorrect.
It's incorrect. The sentence is true.
Her animal spirit is really tough.
Nice.
I choose D7.
(Landmine, counts as incorrect)
- She really is a beast.
- She's bold.
She really is fearless.
Team White's turn.
Time out.
Let's go with the nerves of steel.
I choose G3.
(As of May, 2026, "Avatar"
is the highest-grossing film of all time.)
O.
Correct.
- She's good.
- Really?
- What's going on?
- It's hard to tell now.
The ones left...
I choose E3. Oh, no.
Time out.
I'll wait one more turn.
Let's just go.
I choose E3.
(In Korea, airing the national anthem
at the end of TV broadcasts...)
(is required by law.)
Is it true?
O.
Incorrect.
(Airing the national anthem
is a tradition.)
He said he'd wait one turn.
He's resting too much.
I choose F3.
(The MMCA operates under the Ministry
of Culture, Sports and Tourism.)
X.
Incorrect.
I choose E4.
(The last Harry Potter film is "Harry
Potter and the Deathly Hallows Part 2.")
- True.
- It's false.
O.
Incorrect.
- It really is like a land-grab game.
- Right.
- I'm nervous.
- Who wants to take G4?
I choose F1.
(South Korea's first regular color
TV broadcasts began in 1970.)
X.
Correct.
(It was started to overcome
the economic downturn of the 1980s.)
It's almost neck and neck.
Twenty-two to twenty-three.
(3 question blocks
and 1 mystery block are left.)
He's not answering them.
He's calm, indeed.
(The Venice Film Festival
is the world's oldest film festival.)
(The world's first commercial film
was made by the Lumiere brothers.)
Time out.
I choose A3.
(The Venice Film Festival
is the world's oldest film festival.)
O.
Correct.
Twenty-four.
She's amazing.
(Team Gold has one question left
to secure more than half.)
I choose B3.
Yes. Just go for them
even if they're confusing.
Commercial film.
- No.
- I think it's false.
It's a commercial film.
- No.
- What's the answer?
O.
Correct.
(Team Gold secures more than half.)
It's over.
- Let's go!
- C2.
I choose C2.
X.
- Incorrect.
- It's true?
We have to take that square.
- Won't that be marked incorrect?
- It's incorrect.
You're saying we shouldn't take it
since it will be marked incorrect?
It should be fine, right? I choose G4.
(Tactical support, counts as correct)
What?
It's correct.
Nice.
They really went all out.
They're both amazing.
Round Two of Fact Land Grab is over.
Here are the results.
Team Gold, 25 points.
Team White, 24 points.
- Team Gold won Round Two.
- Amazing.
Well done.
I made a mistake.
I should have used the weapon,
considering the situation.
I think I let my guard down a little.
Maetel was quite good.
I was flustered seeing her
answer many questions in a row.
Izaha went first.
I think I would have won by a lot...
if I had gone first.
Residents competing in the final round,
please head to the battlefield.
Tell us if there's something
you're good at.
I'm pretty confident in general knowledge.
I think Maillard could compete
in the final round.
We have to use the card strategically.
I think you'll have the best judgment
in doing that.
I think the two of us...
could go for general knowledge.
Can two people go?
- I meant one of us.
- One of them.
I was going to sit this quiz out.
They're all so knowledgeable.
They're way better than me.
The reason this war started...
was because of me.
I decided to take on Round Three...
to take responsibility for it.
Residents competing in Round Three,
please go to your spots.
The keyword for Round Three
is general knowledge.
Here's the group going first
in Round Three.
After two rounds,
Team Gold has 44 points,
and Team White has 54 points.
Team White goes first in Round Three.
A difference of ten points.
- Let's go first.
- Nice.
Good luck!
You will have one minute to check
the layout of the questions.
In one minute, the first group
will start choosing questions.
(Fact Land Grab Round 3,
General Knowledge)
(Round 3, General Knowledge)
Round Three has a lot of variables.
An octopus has eight hearts.
Does it not? It doesn't have four.
My son always tells me random facts.
- I should have paid attention.
- Right.
It's okay. Mokgye can do it.
- This is really...
- There are many doable ones.
Some are pretty hard.
Fact Land Grab...
Round Three begins now.
When the whistle blows,
Team White, the first group,
can choose a question.
(Fact Land Grab)
I choose G6.
(In MBTI, E and I stand for
"Expressive" and "Independent.")
Correct.
(They stand for "Extroversion"
and "Introversion.")
I choose F6.
(Different parts of the human tongue
taste different flavors.)
- Correct.
- It's about taste.
- He's an expert.
- Right.
I choose D3.
(Admiral Yi Sun Sin died
at the Battle of Myeongnyang.)
It's false.
Correct.
Did he die at the Battle of Noryang?
- Yes. Noryang. The last battle.
- It's the Battle of Noryang.
I choose C5.
(The name "Google"
came from a misspelling of "googol,")
(which means 10 to the 100th power.)
Correct.
It must be hard to come up
with false answers like that.
They sound right,
but there are many traps.
Right.
I choose G4.
(Nietzsche's Ubermensch is someone
who perfectly follows the deity's will.)
Incorrect.
- Quickly.
- I'll use the Class B Weapon.
That's right.
What's that?
Does it give you another chance?
Keeping the turn.
Team White keeps their turn.
(He quickly uses the weapon
to keep the momentum going.)
I choose G2.
(A camel's hump stores water.)
- Isn't it true?
- It stores fat.
Correct.
(It stores fat.)
I choose B1.
(Mint feels cool because it lowers
the temperature in your mouth.)
Correct.
- He's a food expert.
- He'd know things about food.
I choose F2.
(Moral hazard refers to a state
of complete moral perfection.)
Correct.
I choose E2.
(AI deep learning is modeled
after the human brain's neural networks.)
Correct.
(Maillard takes his time
choosing a question.)
I choose E4.
(Genocide refers to the mass killing
of a group with the intent to destroy it.)
Correct.
He's taking so long
that he's making me nervous.
I choose F7.
(The equator is at 0 degrees latitude.)
Isn't it at zero degrees?
- Incorrect.
- It's true.
It's finally our turn.
Is he going to use another weapon?
Team Gold's turn.
I choose B6.
B6.
(It's scientifically proven that humans
use only 10 percent of their brains.)
Correct.
I choose A4.
(Pilates was designed
to improve women's posture.)
X.
Correct.
It was designed in prison.
(Joseph Pilates developed it
as a rehabilitation exercise in prison.)
I choose B2.
(Cortisol is a hormone whose levels
increase in stressful situations.)
- It's true.
- Correct.
It's cortisol.
I choose D1.
(Melatonin increases in the evening
as light decreases, helping induce sleep.)
O.
Correct.
Mokgye thrives on stage.
I choose E6.
(Stockholm syndrome
is a psychological response...)
(in which victims develop sympathy
or affection for their captors.)
It's true.
Correct.
I choose C4.
(Vitamin D is produced
in the skin when exposed to sunlight.)
O.
Correct.
I choose B7.
(Carbon dioxide takes up the largest share
of greenhouse gas emissions.)
O.
Correct.
(7 answers in a row)
I choose F4.
(Entropy decreases over time.)
X.
Correct.
This is a crisis.
The flow should be broken.
Right.
I choose C7.
(Solar panels can generate electricity
even on cloudy days.)
O.
Correct.
I choose D6.
(The speed of light
is constant in any medium.)
- It would be constant.
- That's true.
O.
Incorrect.
- See? It can be slowed down.
- Really?
- It can be slowed down in many ways.
- This is nice.
Team White's turn.
I choose F1.
(The country with the largest land area
in the world is Russia.)
Correct.
I choose E1.
(The longest bridge in Korea is
the Incheon Bridge,)
(which connects
Yeongjong Island and Songdo.)
Incorrect.
- It's the longest.
- What was the question again?
I choose A3.
(A plastic garbage island
larger than the Korean Peninsula is...)
(located in the middle
of the Pacific Ocean.)
O.
Correct.
I choose G1.
(In medieval European courts, combat was
used as a means of resolving disputes.)
O.
Dual.
Correct.
I choose A7.
(Minors can also get credit cards
in Korea.)
X.
Incorrect.
I knew they could.
(Middle and high school students
can get credit cards.)
I choose G3.
(The prime meridian, which serves
as the basis for world time,)
(is located at the Griffith Observatory
in LA.)
- That's London.
- It's in London.
No.
Maillard!
- Incorrect.
- It's in London!
(It's the Royal Observatory
in Greenwich, London, England.)
They answered about the same number
of questions,
but due to the incorrect answers...
I choose B4.
(Hydrogen is the most abundant element
in the universe.)
O.
Correct.
I choose A5.
(An octopus has 4 hearts.)
X.
Correct.
My son told me like ten times,
but I never listened.
It definitely has more than 1, but not 4.
Right. It's more than one.
I choose B5.
(Coffee beans are a type of bean.)
O.
But they grow on trees.
- Incorrect.
- See? They grow on coffee trees.
We only call them coffee beans.
It's impossible to get a bingo anyway.
Time out.
He's more deliberate than expected.
I choose A1.
(If you fart in space with zero-gravity,
you can gain forward thrust.)
X.
Incorrect.
Go for it.
I choose A2.
(The 100-won coin is
the only currently circulating coin...)
(that features a real historical figure.)
- Correct.
- Yes.
I choose D2.
(An airplane's black box is
painted orange or red...)
(so that it is easier to spot
after an accident.)
Incorrect.
It's confusing.
Keep calm.
They're both very careful.
I choose E3.
(The 100 Years' War between England
and France actually lasted...)
(for about 70 years.)
O.
Incorrect.
(It lasted 116 years,
including periods of truce.)
(Scanning)
All the remaining ones are difficult.
Time out.
Go for the question mark.
The heart of a beast.
I choose D5.
(Tactical support, counts as correct)
- No.
- We should've taken it.
- This is getting fun.
- You can do it.
This is tense.
I choose C6.
(Two question marks in a row)
(Landmine, counts as incorrect)
- A mine.
- It's okay.
Mokgye is a risk-taker.
Exactly.
I choose D4.
(The DMZ is 4km wide in total,)
(extending 2km north and south
of the Military Demarcation Line.)
Is it 2km on both sides?
I don't know.
Incorrect.
Only three apart.
I choose E5.
(Einstein won the Nobel Prize in Physics
for his theory of relativity.)
X.
Correct.
Yes.
(Einstein received the Nobel Prize
in Physics for the photoelectric effect.)
I choose A6.
(A recommended daily sodium intake
for an adult is 5g or more.)
O.
Incorrect.
(WHO recommends less than 2g.)
That's a lot of pressure.
I choose C1.
(The Sangpyeong Tongbo was first issued
during the reign of King Sukjong...)
(and remained
the only widely circulating currency...)
(until the end of the Joseon Dynasty.)
Correct.
(There were other forms of currency
such as the Daebakjeon.)
That's a relief.
Take your time.
Yes, you can wait.
I choose B3.
(Plastic bottles are all recycled in
the same way, regardless of their color.)
O.
Incorrect.
(Colored plastic bottles are recommended
to be separated for recycling.)
Only one away.
Wait if you don't know the answer.
Time out.
(Maillard continues to skip his turn.)
I choose F3.
(The current drug crime report number
in Korea is 127.)
O.
- Incorrect.
- It's incorrect.
- I thought it was correct.
- Me too.
The heart of a beast is about to
go for the question mark.
He's very careful.
- Time out.
- He thinks there are three duds.
Team Gold's turn.
I can't watch this anymore.
I choose D7.
("Seungjeongwon Ilgi"
of the Joseon Dynasty is listed...)
(on the UNESCO Memory
of the World Register.)
O.
Correct.
Yes.
(Team Gold is leading by 1 again.)
- That's so hard.
- That's hard.
I choose F5.
(Landmine, counts as incorrect)
What?
Thank you.
This is intense.
It's really tough.
I choose C2.
(The blood collected
through blood donation...)
(can be stored for a year
after collection.)
- Correct.
- Good job.
I'll use the Class A Weapon.
Is he using the weapon?
What kind of weapon?
He's taking the land.
Team White used the Class A Weapon.
(Maillard stares at the question board.)
I choose D4.
Team White took Team Gold's land.
(Stealing Territory,
steal the opponent's territory)
He used the weapon again...
and took the land I earned.
That actually gives him two points.
He takes the land I had...
and gets one more point.
The gap becomes two.
I was thinking, "I'll answer three more."
(Only one question left
until getting more than half)
He's extremely careful.
Time out.
Team Gold's turn.
(3 questions and 1 question mark remain.)
I choose G7.
(Tactical support, counts as correct)
Good job.
- The heart of a beast.
- Yes, she has the heart of a beast.
Only three left.
Our lives depend on those three questions.
(The Earth rotates faster near the equator
than near the poles.)
(The actual administrative location
of Gimhae International Airport is Busan.)
I choose E7.
(The Earth rotates faster near the equator
than near the poles.)
- Faster...
- No, isn't it slower?
- Isn't that true?
- It's faster.
(The Earth rotates faster near the equator
than near the poles.)
O.
Please.
Correct.
You got it.
Oh, please.
One or two now?
This is so tense.
Either get one more or...
It's 24 to 23.
This is crazy.
(The actual administrative location
of Gimhae International Airport is Busan.)
I choose G5.
Isn't Yangsan the administrative location?
I think it was Busan.
The administrative location.
The administrative location
might be different.
Busan is the administrative location?
The airport is located near Busan.
She must be really nervous.
This will end the game.
(The actual administrative location
of Gimhae International Airport is Busan.)
O.
Correct.
- Yes!
- It's Busan.
- Skip the turn now. She can just skip.
Are we guaranteed to win
even if we get that wrong?
That's what I mean.
This will determine the result.
- It's a tie.
- Do we win if she answers it?
- Yes.
(Only one question remains.)
(Either answer it...)
(or skip the turn.)
I choose C3.
(Mokgye decides to answer the question.)
(According to UN's
Food and Agriculture Organization,)
(coffee is the second most consumed
beverage in the world after water.)
I don't think that's true.
- I think it'd be tea.
- Coke.
It might be coffee.
It could be coffee. You never know.
- I have no idea.
- I think it's coke.
- It's not coke.
- No?
It's either tea or coffee,
and I think it's coffee.
- Really?
- I think it's tea.
(According to UN's
Food and Agriculture Organization,)
(coffee is the second most consumed
beverage in the world after water.)
I choose...
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)